<agreements><agreement><country>AG</country><language>en</language><language_name>English</language_name><publish_date>2014-09-29T20:07:34</publish_date><texts xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="chunkedStoredAgreementText"><agree_text><![CDATA[I Accept]]></agree_text><main_title><![CDATA[Nintendo Network Services Agreement]]></main_title><non_agree_text><![CDATA[I Decline]]></non_agree_text><main_text index="1"><![CDATA[Network Services Agreement

THIS IS AN IMPORTANT AGREEMENT THAT APPLIES TO YOUR USE OF THE NETWORK SERVICES! PLEASE SCROLL DOWN!

If you are under the age of 18, STOP!

You must get your parent or legal guardian to read and accept this Agreement.

Network Services Agreement

Last Updated: September 29, 2014

This is an agreement between you and Nintendo of America Inc. (together with its Affiliates, "Nintendo" or "we" or "us" or "our") that describes your rights to use the Nintendo Network Services. When using the Network Services, you must abide by this Network Services Agreement and all other applicable rules, policies, and notices that are posted on the Nintendo Website or in the Nintendo eShop (collectively, the "Agreement"). By using or accessing a Nintendo Device or the Network Services, or by agreeing to this Agreement in the user interface of a Nintendo Device, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms of this Agreement. Please read this Agreement carefully. If you do not agree to the terms of this Agreement, you may not use any of the Network Services.

For the purposes of this Agreement:

"Affiliates" means entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with Nintendo of America Inc.;

"Content Provider" means the party that grants a license to Digital Content, which may be us, a third party application provider, or a third party game publisher;

"Digital Content" means digitized electronic content made available to you through the Network Services or that is compatible with and authorized by us for use in connection with the Network Services, such as games, videos, music, images, text, applications, and any updates, replacements, or add-on content associated with any of the foregoing;

"Network Account" means an account that you create and maintain for your use of certain Network Services that require an account as permitted herein;

"Network Services" means those services we offer to you from time to time from a Nintendo Device, a personal computer, other devices authorized by Ni]]></main_text><main_text index="2"><![CDATA[ntendo, or online, and may include, without limitation, the Nintendo eShop, access to or delivery of Digital Content or related software, applications, support services, access to Third Party Services, and access to or use of a Network Account, or of information, data, and other materials relating to any of the foregoing, and any additional terms and conditions under which each of the foregoing are provided;

"Nintendo Device" means a Nintendo-branded device that we authorize for use with the Network Services;

"Nintendo eShop" means the shopping services we make available as part of the Network Services that may be accessed through a Nintendo Device (or through any other methods or devices that we may authorize for such access) for purchasing or otherwise acquiring a license to Digital Content and for purchasing other items that we offer from time to time; 

"Nintendo Website" means our websites, including those having home pages located at www.nintendo.com and www.nintendo.net; 

"Third Party Services" means the services, applications, software, and data that are made available by third parties through the Network Services; 

"User Content" means text, images, audio, video, reviews or other content that you create or is licensed to you and that may be accessible and viewable by the public or other Network Service users; and

"User Manual" means the information manuals that we make available to you on your Nintendo Device and at support.nintendo.com, or that we make accessible to you through the Network Services or other methods, including any updates to those manuals that we may post from time to time.

1. Network Services.

Nintendo grants you a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license, subject to the terms of this Agreement, to use the Network Services as permitted under this Agreement solely on a non-commercial basis. You are responsible for any fees or other charges that arise out of your use of the Network Services, such as charges associated with use of the Nintendo eShop or Third Part]]></main_text><main_text index="3"><![CDATA[y Services.

The Network Services may only be used within the United States, Canada, and certain other countries located in the Americas. The Network Services may not work outside of those countries. By using the Network Services outside of those countries, or by designating one of those countries as your region on a Nintendo Device or website, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms of this Agreement. Certain of the Network Services may not be available to you due to legal or technical limitations or your Nintendo Device settings. Please refer to the User Manual for more information on setting up and using the Network Services that are available to you.

The Network Services may permit you to transfer some or all of your data, information, account balances, and Digital Content between Nintendo Devices that you own, or between your Network Accounts. Please refer to the User Manual for more information on this feature.

2. Your Network Account.

A Network Account may be required for use of certain Network Services. You must provide complete, accurate information when creating your Network Account, and revise this information as needed to keep it up-to-date.

Parental consent is required for the creation of a Network Account and for the use of the Network Services by a child under the age of 13. Instructions for providing parental consent are provided during the Network Account setup process. Please review the Nintendo Privacy Notice, located after the end of this Agreement on a Nintendo Device, as well as on Nintendo.com, for more details regarding our privacy practices.

Your Network Account is personal to you. You may not transfer, assign, or sell your Network Account to others. You should protect your Network Account against unauthorized access or use by others, for example by keeping your Network Account password in a secure location. Please notify us immediately if you become aware of any unauthorized access or use of your Network Account. Remove any information relating to your Network Account from your Ni]]></main_text><main_text index="4"><![CDATA[ntendo Device before selling, transferring, or sharing your Nintendo Device with others. Please refer to the User Manual for instructions on information removal.

You are responsible for ensuring that your Network Account is used, whether by you or by others, only as permitted by this Agreement. This includes use of your Network Account to access or use the Network Services. Use of your Network Account in violation of this Agreement may result in suspension or termination of your Network Account and your ability to use the Network Services, and may also result in termination of this Agreement.

You may cancel your Network Account at any time. If you cancel your Network Account, you will lose access to any data, information, or account balance that is associated with that Network Account. Please refer to the User Manual for information on how to cancel your Network Account and for more information.

3. User Content.

You own your User Content. But by entering into this Agreement you grant to Nintendo a worldwide, royalty-free, irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, and sublicenseable license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, distribute, perform, and display User Content that you post or provide in whole or in part and to incorporate your User Content in other works, in any form, media or technology now known or later developed, including for promotional or marketing purposes.

Nintendo takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any User Content posted, stored or uploaded by you or any third party, or for any loss or damage thereto, nor is Nintendo liable for any mistakes, defamation, slander, libel, omissions, falsehoods, obscenity, pornography or profanity you may encounter. Your use of any Nintendo Device or Network Services is at your own risk. As a provider of interactive services, Nintendo is not liable for any statements, representations or User Content provided by our users.

You also consent and agree that Nintendo may access, use, monitor, disclose or preserve information ass]]></main_text><main_text index="5"><![CDATA[ociated with your use of the Network Services, including, without limitation, your personal information and User Content, or information that Nintendo acquires about you through your use of a Nintendo Device or Network Service when Nintendo forms a good faith belief that doing so is necessary (a) to comply with applicable law or to respond to legal process from competent authorities; (b) to enforce this agreement or protect the rights or property rights of Nintendo, its users, or the public; (c) to help prevent a loss of life or serious physical injury to anyone; or (d) prevent potentially illegal or offensive activities.

4. Shopping Services.

You may establish and maintain an account balance for purchasing items we offer and sell in the Nintendo eShop. That account balance is associated solely with your Network Account, is subject to balance and usage limits or restrictions that we may impose from time to time, and may not be transferred to third parties. That account balance may not be used to purchase items that are offered or sold by others or that are sold outside of the Nintendo eShop. Please refer to the User Manual for more information about the Nintendo eShop features.

You are responsible for any purchases, downloads, or other content acquisitions made using your Network Account in Nintendo eShop. Nintendo eShop purchases are non-refundable and non-transferable unless otherwise stated in the terms posted for a specific offer or required by law. Digital Content is licensed, not sold, from the Content Provider to you solely for your personal, non-commercial use on your Nintendo Device or as we permit through the Network Services, subject to the terms of this Agreement and any additional terms posted for that Digital Content item in Nintendo eShop and subject to your payment in full for that Digital Content. Digital Content licenses that are purchased through your Nintendo Account and downloaded to a Nintendo Device may be available for access and use through other Nintendo Accounts on that Nintendo Devi]]></main_text><main_text index="6"><![CDATA[ce.

Nintendo eShop may support other Network Services, such as services that allow you to access, view, or download Digital Content to your Nintendo Device, to review other items that may be purchased in connection with a Nintendo Device or the Network Services, to review your purchase history or, if supported on your Nintendo Device, to use points to make purchases in the Wii shop during operation in Wii compatible mode.

5. Third Party Services.

We are not responsible for any Third Party Services you elect to access or use, and we are not responsible for any charges or other liabilities that arise out of your use of Third Party Services. Third Party Services are not reviewed or monitored by us and are subject to separate third party terms and conditions associated with such Third Party Services. Nintendo’s Privacy Notice does not apply to Third Party Services. You access and use Third Party Services solely at your own risk.

6. Use of Information.

We may collect, use and disclose personal information that (a) you provide to us; (b) we collect automatically; and (c) we receive from other sources. Please refer to Nintendo’s Privacy Notice, located after the end of this Agreement, as well as on Nintendo.com, for information on how we collect, use and disclose information from our users. The Nintendo Privacy Notice applies to all of our products, services and websites, including the Network Services. We recommend that you review Nintendo’s Privacy Notice before each use of the Network Services or a Nintendo Device or website to help you stay informed of our privacy practices.

7. Code of Conduct.

To help keep the Network Services friendly and safe for all users, you will not engage in any harmful, illegal, or otherwise offensive conduct, such as:

 A. Misrepresenting, impersonating, abusing, stalking, threatening, or harassing any person or company, such as other users, us, or our employees, representatives, moderators, or contractors;

 B. Engaging in any discriminatory, defamatory, hateful, harassing, abusive]]></main_text><main_text index="7"><![CDATA[, obscene, threatening, physically dangerous, or otherwise objectionable conduct in connection with a Nintendo Device or the Network Services; 

 C. Making, disseminating, sharing, or playing unauthorized copies of games, music, or images on a Nintendo Device or the Network Services; this activity is illegal! 

 D. Making new versions of Digital Content or a Nintendo Device;

 E. Trying to modify or gain unauthorized access to another person’s Nintendo Device or Network Account or trying to modify, reverse engineer, or gain unauthorized or automated access to any of Nintendo’s computers, hardware, software, or networks used to provide the Network Services or any feature of a Nintendo Device; 

 F. Cheating in a game, unless such cheats have been deliberately enabled by the Content Provider; 

 G. Hosting, intercepting, emulating, reverse engineering, or redirecting the communication protocols used by Nintendo as part of a Nintendo Device or the Network Services, regardless of the method used to do so; or do anything that might bypass or circumvent measures employed to prevent or limit access to any area, content or code of any Nintendo Device or Network Services (except as otherwise expressly permitted by law); 

 H. Developing any third-party applications that interact with User Content and the Network Services without our prior written consent;

 I. Engaging in any commercial activity using a Nintendo Device or the Network Services or any other activity that disrupts, diminishes the quality of, interferes with the performance of, or impairs the functionality of a Nintendo Device, the Network Services, or any Third Party Services;

 J. Using any robot, spider, crawler, scraper or other automated means or interface not provided by us to access or extract data from any Nintendo Device or Network Services; or

 K. Uploading, posting, emailing, transmitting, or otherwise making available: (i) any content or data that you do not have a legal right to make available; (ii) any content or data that infringes any patent,]]></main_text><main_text index="8"><![CDATA[ trademark, trade secret, copyright, or other intellectual property or proprietary right of any party; (iii) any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising or promotional materials; (iv) content or data of which you have disguised the origin; (v) viruses, corrupted data or other harmful, disruptive or destructive files (vi) content or data that contains private information of any third party, including, without limitation, names, addresses, email address or credit card information; or (vii) content or data that is obscene, is unlawful, violates this Agreement, or is prohibited from publication in your jurisdiction.

8. Reservation of Rights and Interests.

The Network Services are provided to you on a limited license basis, and are not sold to you. Other than your limited license to use the Network Services as expressly provided in this Agreement, we retain all right, title, and interest in and to the Network Services including, without limitation, all associated patent, copyright, and trademark rights, and all other proprietary or intellectual property rights of any kind in any country.

9. Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability.

USE OF THE NETWORK SERVICES AND THE THIRD PARTY SERVICES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY NINTENDO OR ITS REPRESENTATIVES CREATES A WARRANTY. THE NETWORK SERVICES ARE PROVIDED "AS-IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. NINTENDO DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO THE NETWORK SERVICES AND THIRD PARTY SERVICES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTY OF NON-INFRINGEMENT, OR THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, NINTENDO WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO YOUR ACCESS, USE, MISUSE, OR INABILITY TO USE THE NETWORK SERVICES OR ANY THIRD PARTY SERVICES, EVEN IF NINTENDO HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN ANY CASE, NINTENDO’S AGGREGATE LIABILITY T]]></main_text><main_text index="9"><![CDATA[O YOU IN CONNECTION WITH ANY CLAIMS ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE NETWORK SERVICES AND THE THIRD PARTY SERVICES IS LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT YOU ACTUALLY PAID FOR THE NETWORK SERVICES THAT ARE THE SUBJECT OF SUCH CLAIM. IF A LAW RESTRICTS OUR ABILITY TO LIMIT LIABILITY OR DISCLAIM WARRANTIES, THE LIMITATIONS LISTED ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN THAT CASE, WE LIMIT OUR LIABILITY AND DISCLAIM WARRANTIES TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

10. Indemnity.

If we or any of our Affiliates, licensees, licensors, or contractors are subject to any actual or threatened claims, costs, damages, losses, or other liabilities (collectively, "Covered Losses") as a result of your use of any of the Network Services, Digital Content, a Nintendo Device, or any data, information, or other item you make available through the Network Services or a Nintendo Device including User Content, then you agree to indemnify us (and our affiliates, licensees, licensors, contractors, and employees) from all such Covered Losses and any related costs, such as reasonable attorney’s fees.

11. Feedback.

Separate and apart from User Content, you can generally submit questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, plans, notes, drawings, original or creative materials or other information or materials about Nintendo and the Network Services ("Feedback"). Feedback, whether submitted through the Network Services or otherwise, is non-confidential and shall become the sole property of Nintendo. We shall own exclusive rights, including all intellectual property rights, in and to such Feedback and shall be entitled to the unrestricted use and dissemination of this Feedback for any purpose, commercial or otherwise, without acknowledgment or compensation to you.

12. Dispute Resolution; Binding Individual Arbitration; Class Action Waiver.

 A. Our consumer service department is available to address any concerns you may have regarding your Network Account or the Network Services. You may contact them by phone at 1-800-255-3700, by email at useragreement@noa.nin]]></main_text><main_text index="10"><![CDATA[tendo.com, or by regular mail sent to Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: User Agreement, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052 USA. Most matters are quickly resolved in this manner to our customer’s satisfaction. Any matter we are unable to resolve and all disputes or claims arising out of or relating to this Agreement, including its formation, enforceability, performance, or breach (each, a "Claim"), with the exception of the matters described in section 12(C) below, shall be finally settled by binding arbitration administered by the American Arbitration Association in accordance with the provisions of its Commercial Arbitration Rules and the supplementary procedures for consumer related disputes of the American Arbitration Association (the "AAA"), excluding any rules or procedures governing or permitting class actions. The arbitrator, and not any federal, state or local court or agency, shall have exclusive authority to resolve all Claims. The arbitrator shall be empowered to grant whatever relief would be available in a court under law or in equity. The arbitrator’s award shall be binding on the parties and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. The parties understand that, absent this mandatory provision, they would have the right to sue in court and have a jury trial. They further understand that, in some instances, the costs of arbitration could exceed the costs of litigation and the right to discovery may be more limited in arbitration than in court. Any such arbitration shall be conducted by the parties in their individual capacities only and not as a class action or other representative action, and the parties waive their right to file a class action or seek relief on a class basis. If any court or arbitrator determines that the class action waiver set forth in the preceding sentence is void or unenforceable for any reason or that an arbitration can proceed on a class basis, then the arbitration provision set forth in this Section 12 shall be deemed null and void in its entirety]]></main_text><main_text index="11"><![CDATA[ and the parties shall be deemed to have not agreed to arbitrate Claims.

 B. The rules governing the arbitration may be accessed at www.adr.org or by calling the AAA at +1.800.778.7879. To the extent the initial filing fee for the arbitration exceeds the initial filing fee for a lawsuit, we will pay the difference in fees. If the arbitrator finds the arbitration to be non-frivolous, we will pay all of the actual filing and arbitrator fees for the arbitration, provided your claim is less than $75,000. The arbitration rules also permit you to recover attorney’s fees in certain cases.

 C. Section 12(A) does not apply to any Claim (i) in which a party is attempting to protect its intellectual property rights (such as its patent, copyright, trademark, trade secret, or moral rights, but not including its privacy or publicity rights), or (ii) that may be brought in small claims court.

 D. 30-Day Right to Opt Out: You have the right to opt out of the provisions of this Section 12 by sending written notice of your decision to opt out to the following address: Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: CS Admin, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052 within 30 days of creating your Network Account. Your notice should include your account number. If you send this notice, then Section 12 will not apply to either party. If you do not send this notice, then you agree to be bound by this Section 12.

13. General.

 A. Breach; Termination; Survival. This Agreement will automatically terminate if you do not comply with this Agreement. Upon any such termination, you must immediately cease all use of the Network Services. Sections 3, 5, 6, 8, 9, 10, 12 and 13 of this Agreement will remain in effect following any such termination.

 B. Changes to Network Services; Delivery of Network Services. We may modify, cancel, or suspend the availability of the Network Services in whole or in part at any time without notice to you. We may involve Affiliates or third parties in the delivery of the Network Services or in the performance of our obligations]]></main_text><main_text index="12"><![CDATA[ under this Agreement.

 C. Enforcement; Non-waiver; Non-assignment. If any part of this Agreement is held to be invalid or unenforceable, that part will no longer apply to the parties and will be replaced by an enforceable provision that most closely reflects the original intent of the parties, but all other parts of the Agreement will remain in effect unless otherwise provided in this Agreement. Our failure to insist upon or enforce your strict compliance with this Agreement will not constitute a waiver of any of our rights. You may not assign your rights or interests under this Agreement to any other person.

 D. Governing Law. The laws of the state of Washington, U.S.A., without regard to its conflict of laws provisions, will govern this Agreement and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Nintendo.

 E. Venue. If Section 12 is held to be invalid or unenforceable, then for any Claims the parties consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in King County, Washington, U.S.A.

 F. No Third-Party Beneficiaries. This Agreement is for the benefit of, and will be enforceable by, the parties only, and is not intended to confer any right or benefit on any third party or to create any obligations to any such third party.

 G. Changes to Terms. We may change the terms of this Agreement at any time without notice. A current version of this Agreement, including any changes, is posted at support.nintendo.com for your convenience. If you do not agree to any changes to this Agreement, you must cancel your Network Account and discontinue use of the Network Services.

 H. Notices. To contact our consumer service department regarding this Agreement, you may (i) send an email to useragreement@noa.nintendo.com; (ii) send a letter to Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: User Agreement, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052 USA; or (iii) call, toll free 1-888-977-7627. Your communications with our consumer service department will not constitute legal notice where required by the Agreement or by law.

 Fo]]></main_text><main_text index="13"><![CDATA[r all other legal matters, you must contact or notify us in writing at: Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: General Counsel, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052.

 We may notify you regarding this Agreement by: (i) email at the address associated with your Network Account; or (ii) through posted messages in the Nintendo eShop, the Nintendo Website, or other locations that we specify to you from time to time. These notices will be effective as of the date of delivery or posting. Please be sure to keep the email address associated with your Network Account up-to-date.

 I. Notices and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement. Nintendo respects the intellectual property of others and we ask users of Nintendo products and services to do the same. If you feel that your intellectual property rights have been infringed, please visit www.nintendo.com/ippolicy to read our full policy and to submit a takedown request.

*** End of Network Services Agreement ***




Nintendo Privacy Notice

Last Updated: July 2, 2015

Nintendo knows that privacy is important to you. This Privacy Notice describes how we collect, use, disclose, store and protect your information. By using a Nintendo product or service, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

1. YOUR INFORMATION

Information you provide to us. We collect information that you provide to us when you use our products and services or anytime you are in contact with us.

Some types of information you may provide include:

 * Registration information that you may be required to provide when you sign up to use our services, including your name, address, telephone number, and email address;
 * Login information that you use to sign in to our services, such as your username and password;
 * Demographic information about you, including your age, gender, hobbies, interests, and country of residence;
 * Payment information that you submit, including your credit card number, expiration date, and credit card security code, where needed to complete a trans]]></main_text><main_text index="14"><![CDATA[action you have initiated;
 * Messages, photos, videos, drawings, audio recordings and other information shared by you through the interactive features of our products and services;
 * Correspondence you send directly to us; and
 * Information you provide to us offline (through, for example, regular mail, in-person sweepstakes entry forms, and consumer service transactions such as repairs, part orders and direct purchases).

Information we collect automatically. We collect some information automatically when you use our products and services.

Some types of information we collect automatically include:

 * Information about your use of our products, services and websites, including your browser type, operating system, platform, IP address, MAC address, language and region; 
 * Information about websites you visited before and after visiting our websites, search queries that landed you on our websites, search queries you conducted on our websites, and pages and advertisements you viewed and links you clicked on while using our websites;
 * Information about your Nintendo device including device serial number, device ID, wireless access point, and other technical information about your device; and
 * Information about your game play, online status, use of our online services, friends and friend codes, purchases, and other information about your interactions with our products and services.

Information we receive from other sources. We may receive information about you from other sources, including through third-party services and retailers.

Some examples of information we may receive from other sources include:

 * Navigation data, including websites visited and advertisements viewed or clicked;
 * Information about consumer service transactions; and 
 * Purchase information.

Please note that we may add information we receive from other sources to the information we already have about you. We also may combine your information with information about other users, including game play, demographic, search term, click]]></main_text><main_text index="15"><![CDATA[stream and purchase information, and use this combined information in an aggregated format.

2. COOKIES, WEB BEACONS, LOG FILES AND THIRD PARTY PARTNERS

In order to collect some of the information described above, we may use Web beacons, cookies, log files, and similar technologies in some of our products and services, including our emails.

 * Web Beacons: We may use web beacons (also referred to as pixel trackers or clear GIFs), which are small graphic images placed on a webpage, on a web-based document, or in an email message. Web beacons are designed to collect certain user information and monitor certain user activity. Information collected by web beacons might include your IP address, MAC address, the URL of the page you came from, or your interactions with our website or an email message we send to you. We may use the information collected through web beacons, for example, to determine how to improve certain products and services by identifying popular webpages, services, features, and products; to personalize our products and services; to make recommendations for products and services; and to complete transactions you have requested.
 * Cookies: We may use cookies, which are unique identifiers that are sometimes placed on your device to record data about your visits to a website, so that the site can recognize your device and personalize your visit. Information collected by cookies may be linked to your transaction history, online game play or other information. We may use information collected by cookies, for example, to determine how to improve certain products and services by identifying popular webpages, services, features, and products; to personalize our products and services; to make recommendations for products and services; and to complete transactions you have requested. You can set certain browsers to reject cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. However, not utilizing cookies may prevent you from using certain functions and features of our products and services.
 * Log Files: We]]></main_text><main_text index="16"><![CDATA[ maintain log files which record activity related to the use of our products and services, such as the number of hits a particular webpage has received, the type and quality of a user’s Internet connection, the type of hardware and/or software used to access a particular service, which features of a service are used and their frequency of use. The entries within these log files may include, for example, your IP addresses, MAC addresses, cookie information, device ID, transactional data, device settings, and download activity. We may use these log files, for example, to monitor traffic on our website, to facilitate use of certain services and to troubleshoot technical problems.
 * Third Party Partners: We also may permit our third party partners to set cookies, web beacons and similar technologies on our websites, or within emails sent on our behalf, to help us perform various internal functions necessary to operate our business. These third parties may also use these cookies and Web beacons, and other technologies to collect information about your visits to our websites and elsewhere on the Internet and may use that information during, or after, your visits to our websites to provide you advertisements across the Internet about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Some of these third parties may offer you a way to opt-out of this type ad targeting through industry choice mechanisms. To learn more about third parties that participate in these choice offering and to exercise choices that may be available to you, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org and www.aboutads.info.

3. USE OF INFORMATION

We may use your information in order for us, our affiliated companies, or our third party partners, to: (i) fulfill your requests for products, services, and information, including to send you commercial and non-commercial messages and to process orders you have placed; (ii) contact you in connection with our products and services, including for marketing and promotional purposes; (iii) facilitate your use ]]></main_text><main_text index="17"><![CDATA[of our products, services and websites; (iv) enable your participation in online games, contests, sweepstakes, surveys, public forums, and other features offered through our products, services and websites; (v) make recommendations and customize the content, features, and advertising available through our products, services and websites and on other’s websites; (vi) set up repair orders and respond to consumer service inquiries; (vii) provide back-end services, including system updates, system messages; (viii) provide free games, applications, trials, and other content; (ix) analyze and facilitate the use of our products, services and websites; (x) facilitate demographic studies; (xi) understand, improve, and develop our products, services and websites; (xii) prevent potentially illegal or offensive activities; (xiii) enforce our rights or the rights of our users; (xiv) verify your identity and prevent fraudulent transactions; and (xv) for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent.

4. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

At times we may make certain information that we collect available to our affiliated companies, to our third party partners, to other Nintendo users, to the general public and for other legal and business purposes. For example: 

 * Nintendo Affiliates. We may share information with other Nintendo affiliated companies that use it consistent with this Privacy Notice.
 * Third Parties. We may share information with our third party partners to help us perform various functions necessary to operate our business or fulfill your requests (for example, helping you process your downloads or purchases, and developing and executing marketing campaigns). We also may share such information to, for example, complete your transactions, provide you with advertising and other promotional materials, and assist in the creation of user accounts with third parties.
 * Other Users and Friends. We may share information, including, for example, your user name, Mii pr]]></main_text><main_text index="18"><![CDATA[ofile information, online status, Mii greeting, and other game play information, with other Nintendo users when you use the online features of our products and services.
 * General Public. When you use some of our online services, for example, when you play games online or post to Miiverse, your user name, nickname, user profile and certain gameplay information may be displayed on the internet and be seen by the general public.
 * Local Communications. Some Nintendo devices have local communication features that can be activated by you. These features allow some of your information to be automatically collected by and shared with us and with other Nintendo users. These features also allow us, and other Nintendo users, to automatically contact and interact with you. When these features are enabled by you, you may receive information about, and communications from, other Nintendo users, and you may also receive advertising and promotional materials from Nintendo and its third party partners. You may disable these local communication features at any time through the system settings on your Nintendo device.
 * Legal and Business Purposes. We may disclose your information in order to comply with legal process, to respond to claims or inquiries, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of Nintendo, our users, or the public. Your information may also be disclosed as part of any sale or transfer of company assets, if legally permitted.

You are responsible for any information that you share with others through use of our products, services, and websites. Please be aware that other users may be able to store, modify, or share with third parties, information that you provide to them.

5. LINKING ACCOUNTS

We may offer you an account for one or more of our loyalty programs, including Club Nintendo, so that you have the opportunity to receive personalized content and participate in a variety of activities, promotions and programs. Within certain parameters, you may be able to link your Nintendo device or network]]></main_text><main_text index="19"><![CDATA[ account to your loyalty account. In such circumstances, we will use your information to, for example, automatically register your purchases in your loyalty account so that you have the opportunity to receive rewards and promotions. You may unlink these accounts in the settings section of the Nintendo eShop.

6. THIRD-PARTIES

You may disclose your information to third parties when you use our products and services in order to play third-party games, use third-party applications or plugins, view third-party advertisements, or visit third-party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties, and we recommend that you review their privacy policies before submitting any information.

7. ATTENTION PARENTS OR LEGAL GUARDIANS: PROTECTING CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

In accordance with applicable law, we obtain consent from parents for the collection of personal information from their children. You can find information about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information from our users, including children under the age of 13, in the sections above titled YOUR INFORMATION, USE OF INFORMATION, DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION.

You may review, and have deleted, the personal information we have collected from your child, and you may refuse to permit our further collection or use of your child’s personal information, by contacting a Nintendo Privacy Administrator via email at privacypolicy@noa.nintendo.com, by phone at 1-888-977-7627, or by regular mail at Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: Nintendo Privacy Administrator, 4600 150th Avenue NE, Redmond, WA 98052, U.S.A. Before responding to your request to review personal information collected from your child, we may require that you follow reasonable procedures to help verify your identity as the child’s parent or legal guardian. We may deny any request that fails to follow these procedures. If you choose to have your child’s personal information deleted, or refuse to permit further collection or use of your child’s personal information, certain feat]]></main_text><main_text index="20"><![CDATA[ures of our products and services may be limited or unavailable.

Please note that third-party game publishers, application providers, and content providers may collect, use, and disclose your child’s personal information through our products and services when your child uses third-party’s services or content. Nintendo is not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties, and we recommend that you review their privacy notices before your child provides or exchanges any personal information through third-party services or content.

We strongly recommend that you supervise your child’s use of our products and services at all times. You can restrict your children’s use of certain features of our products and services by setting up the parental controls on your Nintendo device. For a detailed description of these parental control features, please see the user manual for your Nintendo device.

8. SECURITY

Nintendo uses reasonable measures, and has established reasonable safeguards, to help protect your information from loss, theft, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. You should understand that no data storage system or transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

Please note that information collected by third parties may not have the same security protections as information you submit to us or that we collect, and we are not responsible for protecting the security of such information.

If you install unauthorized applications or content on, or make unauthorized modifications to, your Nintendo device or its software, your information may be compromised. Nintendo is not responsible for any collection, use or disclosure of information from any Nintendo device that has unauthorized modifications or contains unauthorized software or content.

9. OPTING-OUT

You may use a Nintendo device without providing us your information; however, some features and applications may not be available to you. You can opt-out of]]></main_text><main_text index="21"><![CDATA[ the collection of certain information by not using our services. You also may be able to opt-out of certain types of information collection through your Nintendo device settings, parental controls or other opt-out mechanisms we make available to you. Certain aggregated technical information about your Nintendo device may still be automatically collected when you, or another user of your device, connects to the internet. You may opt out of receiving commercial email messages from Nintendo by following the instructions contained in any such email message.

10. REMOVING INFORMATION STORED ON YOUR NINTENDO DEVICE

Certain information about you may be stored on your Nintendo device. For your protection, before selling, transferring, or otherwise disposing of your Nintendo device, please remove all stored information, including information stored on any of the device’s accessories. For instructions on how to remove stored information from your Nintendo device, please see the user manual or visit support.nintendo.com.

If you transfer data from one Nintendo device to another, using any of our system transfer tools or features, any information about you, that is stored on that device, will be transferred as part of the process.

11. INTERNATIONAL USERS

Any information you provide, or that is collected through use of our products, services, or websites, may be stored, processed, and transferred within, or to, the United States, or any other country in which we or our affiliated companies or third party partners maintain facilities. As a result, it is possible that your information could be accessed by foreign governmental authorities, or otherwise, in accordance with applicable local laws. By using our US based website, or by designating the United States as the region for your Nintendo device, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States. We abide by the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor ]]></main_text><main_text index="22"><![CDATA[Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework, as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce, regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Economic Area and Switzerland. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor website.

12. CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY NOTICE

We may update this Privacy Notice from time to time. When we update this Privacy Notice, we will revise the "Last Updated" date above. Updates will be posted at support.nintendo.com. We recommend that you review this Privacy Notice each time you use our products, services, or websites to help you stay informed of our privacy practices.

13. ESRB CERTIFICATION

This Privacy Notice and the certification seal located on our website confirms that we are a valid licensee, and participating member, of the Entertainment Software Rating Board’s Privacy Certified Program. To help protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative. As a licensee in this privacy certification program, we are subject to frequent audits of our websites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB. All of our websites containing the ESRB certification seal have been reviewed, and certified, by ESRB to meet established online information collection and use practices.

14. CONTACT US WITH YOUR PRIVACY QUESTIONS, COMMENTS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions, complaints or comments regarding this Privacy Notice, or any of our privacy practices, please contact a Nintendo Privacy Administrator via email at privacypolicy@noa.nintendo.com, via phone at 1-888-977-7627, or via regular mail at Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: Privacy Administrator, 4600 150th Avenue NE, Redmond, WA 98052, U.S.A.

You may also contact ESRB Privacy Certified via email at privacy@esrb.org, or via regular mail at ESRB Privacy Certified, Attn: Privacy Certified Program, 420 Lexington Avenue, Suite 2024, New York, NY 10017.
]]></main_text></texts><type>NINTENDO-NETWORK-EULA</type><version>0300</version></agreement><agreement><country>AG</country><language>es</language><language_name>Español</language_name><publish_date>2014-09-29T20:07:36</publish_date><texts xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="chunkedStoredAgreementText"><agree_text><![CDATA[Acepto]]></agree_text><main_title><![CDATA[Acuerdo de Servicios de red de Nintendo]]></main_title><non_agree_text><![CDATA[No acepto]]></non_agree_text><main_text index="1"><![CDATA[Acuerdo de Servicios de red de Nintendo

¡ESTE ES UN ACUERDO IMPORTANTE QUE SE APLICA AL USO QUE LE DA A LOS SERVICIOS DE RED! ¡DESPLÁCESE HACIA ABAJO!

Si tiene menos de 18 años de edad, ¡DETÉNGASE!

Debe llamar a su padre/madre o tutor legal para que lea y acepte este Acuerdo.

Acuerdo de Servicios de red de Nintendo

Última actualización: 29 de septiembre de 2014

Este es un acuerdo celebrado entre usted y Nintendo of America Inc. (conjuntamente con sus Filiales "Nintendo" o "nosotros" o "nuestro") que describe sus derechos para usar los Servicios de red. Cuando se usen los Servicios de red, usted deberá acatar el Acuerdo de Servicios de red de Nintendo y todas las otras normas, políticas y notificaciones aplicables que se publican en el Sitio web de Nintendo (Nintendo Website) o en la Tienda virtual de Nintendo (Nintendo eShop) (colectivamente, el "Acuerdo"). Al usar o acceder al Dispositivo Nintendo o los Servicios de red, o al convenir en los términos de este Acuerdo en la interfaz de usuario de un Dispositivo Nintendo, usted acepta estar sujeto a los términos del presente Acuerdo. Lea atentamente este Acuerdo. Si no está de acuerdo con los términos del presente Acuerdo, no podrá usar ninguno de los Servicios de red.

Para los propósitos del presente Acuerdo:

"Afiliados" hace referencia a las entidades que controlan, son controladas por, o están bajo el control común de Nintendo of America Inc.;

"Proveedor de contenidos" hace referencia a la parte que otorga una licencia para el Contenido digital, que puede ser nosotros, un proveedor externo de aplicaciones o un editor externo de juegos;

"Contenido digital" hace referencia al contenido electrónico digitalizado al que usted puede acceder mediante los Servicios de red o que es compatible con los Servicios de red y nosotros autorizamos su uso en conexión con dichos servicios, como por ejemplo, juegos, videos, música, imágenes, texto, aplicaciones y cualquier actualización, reemplazo o contenido adicional relacionado con cualquiera de lo antes mencionado;

"]]></main_text><main_text index="2"><![CDATA[Cuenta de red" hace referencia a una cuenta que usted crea y mantiene para usar ciertos Servicios de red que exigen una cuenta, según lo permitido por el presente;

"Servicios de red" hace referencia a aquellos servicios que le ofrecemos periódicamente, desde un Dispositivo Nintendo, una computadora personal, otros dispositivos autorizados por Nintendo, o en línea, y pueden incluir, entre otros, la Tienda virtual de Nintendo, el acceso o la entrega de Contenido digital o software relacionado, aplicaciones, servicios de asistencia, acceso a los Servicios de terceros y acceso o uso de una Cuenta de red, o información, datos y otros materiales relacionados con cualquiera de lo antes mencionado, y cualquier término y condición adicional en virtud del cual se brinde cada uno de los antes mencionados;

"Dispositivo Nintendo" hace referencia a un dispositivo de marca Nintendo que autorizamos se use con los Servicios de red;

"Tienda virtual de Nintendo" hace referencia a los servicios de compra disponibles como parte de los Servicios de red a los que se pueden acceder mediante un Dispositivo Nintendo (o a través de cualquier otro método o dispositivo que podamos autorizar para dicho acceso) para comprar, o de otro modo, adquirir, una licencia de Contenido digital y comprar otros artículos que ofrezcamos periódicamente;

"Sitio web de Nintendo" hace referencia a nuestros sitios web, incluidos aquellos que cuentan con las páginas principales ubicadas en www.nintendo.com y www.nintendo.net;

"Servicios de terceros" hace referencia a servicios, aplicaciones, software y datos que brindan terceros a través de los Servicios de red;

"Contenido de usuario" hace referencia a texto, imágenes, audio, video, análisis u otro contenido que usted crea o que está autorizado mediante licencia para usted, y que puede ser accesible y visible por el público u otros usuarios de Servicios de red; y

"Manual del usuario" hace referencia a los manuales de información que le ofrecemos en su Dispositivo Nintendo y en support.nintendo.com, o a lo]]></main_text><main_text index="3"><![CDATA[s que puede acceder a través de los Servicios de red u otros métodos, lo que incluye cualquier actualización para los manuales que podamos publicar periódicamente.

1. Servicios de red.

Nintendo le otorga una licencia personal, no exclusiva, intransferible, revocable, sujeta a los términos del presente Acuerdo, para usar los Servicios de red según lo permitido en virtud de este Acuerdo únicamente con fines no comerciales. Usted es responsable de cualquier tarifa o cargo que surja por su uso de los Servicios de red, por ejemplo, cargos relacionados con el uso de la Tienda virtual de Nintendo o Servicios de terceros.

Los Servicios de red solo podrán usarse dentro de los Estados Unidos, Canadá y algunos otros países ubicados en América. Los Servicios de red podrían no funcionar fuera de estos países. Al usar estos Servicios de red fuera de estos países o al designar uno de esos países como su región en un Dispositivo o sitio web de Nintendo, usted acepta someterse a los términos del presente Acuerdo. Es posible que algunos de los Servicios de red no se encuentren disponibles debido a limitaciones legales o técnicas, o a la configuración de su Dispositivo Nintendo. Sírvase consultar el Manual del usuario para obtener más información sobre la configuración y uso de los Servicios de red que se encuentran disponibles para usted.

Los Servicios de red pueden permitirle transferir algunos o todos los datos, información, saldos de cuenta y Contenido digital a los Dispositivos Nintendo que posee, o a sus Cuentas de red. Sírvase consultar el Manual del usuario para obtener más información sobre esta función.

2. Su Cuenta de red.

Es posible que necesite una Cuenta de red para poder usar determinados Servicios de red. Usted deberá proporcionar información correcta y completa al crear su Cuenta de red, y revisar esta información según sea necesario para mantenerla actualizada.

Se requiere el consentimiento de los padres para que un niño menor de 13 años cree una Cuenta de red y haga uso de los Servicios de red. Durante el ]]></main_text><main_text index="4"><![CDATA[proceso de configuración de la Cuenta de red se brindan instrucciones para proveer el consentimiento de los padres. Sírvase revisar la Política de privacidad de Nintendo, ubicada al final del presente Acuerdo en un Dispositivo Nintendo, así como en Nintendo.com para obtener más detalles respecto de nuestras prácticas de privacidad.

Su Cuenta de red es personal. No puede transferir, asignar o vender su Cuenta de red a otros. Debe proteger su Cuenta de red contra el acceso o uso no autorizado de otras personas; por ejemplo mediante el uso de una contraseña de Cuenta de red en una ubicación segura. Sírvase notificarnos inmediatamente si se da cuenta de algún acceso o uso no autorizado en su Cuenta de red. Elimine cualquier información relacionada con su Cuenta de red de su Dispositivo Nintendo antes de vender, transferir o compartir su Dispositivo Nintendo con otras personas. Sírvase consultar el Manual del usuario para obtener las instrucciones sobre cómo eliminar información.

Usted es responsable de garantizar que usted u otras personas usan su Cuenta de red solo según lo permitido por el presente Acuerdo. Esto incluye el uso de su Cuenta de red para acceder o usar los Servicios de red. El uso de su Cuenta de red en violación del presente Acuerdo puede resultar en la suspensión o terminación de su Cuenta de red y su capacidad para usar los Servicios de red, y también puede resultar en la rescisión del presente Acuerdo.

Puede cancelar su Cuenta de red en cualquier momento. Si cancela su Cuenta de red, perderá el acceso a cualquier dato, información o saldo de cuenta relacionado con dicha Cuenta de red. Consulte el Manual del usuario para obtener más información sobre cómo cancelar su Cuenta de red, así como información adicional.

3. Contenido para el usuario.

Usted es dueño del Contenido para el usuario. Pero, al aceptar este Acuerdo usted le concede a Nintendo a nivel mundial, una licencia libre de regalías, irrevocable, perpetua, sin exclusividad y subtransferible para usar, reproducir, modificar, adaptar, p]]></main_text><main_text index="5"><![CDATA[ublicar, traducir, distribuir, ejecutar y mostrar Contenido para el usuario que usted publique o proporcione, en su totalidad o en forma parcial, y para incorporar su Contenido para el usuario en otras tareas, en cualquier forma, medio o tecnología conocida actualmente o desarrollada más adelante, incluidos fines promocionales o de marketing.

Nintendo no se responsabiliza ni asume ninguna responsabilidad de ningún Contenido para el usuario publicado, almacenado o cargado por usted o cualquier tercero, o de cualquier pérdida o daño de esta, así como tampoco se responsabiliza de los posibles errores, difamaciones, calumnias, injurias, omisiones, falsedades, obscenidades, pornografía o lenguaje vulgar que usted pueda encontrar. El uso de cualquier Dispositivo Nintendo o del Servicio de red es bajo su propio riesgo. Como proveedor de servicios interactivos, Nintendo no se hace responsable de las declaraciones, manifestaciones o Contenido para el usuario proporcionado por nuestros usuarios.

A la vez, usted consiente y está de acuerdo que Nintendo pueda acceder, supervisar, utilizar, revelar o conservar la información asociada con su uso de los Servicios de red, incluso, sin limitación, su información personal y Contenido para el usuario, o información personal que Nintendo obtiene a través de su uso de un Dispositivo Nintendo o Servicio de red, cuando Nintendo cree conveniente y necesario hacerlo para (a) cumplir con la ley aplicable o responder al proceso judicial de autoridades competentes; (b) hacer cumplir este acuerdo o proteger los derechos o propiedad de Nintendo, sus usuarios o el público; (c) ayudar a prevenir una pérdida de vida o daño físico serio a alguien; o (d) evitar actividades potencialmente ilegales u ofensivas.

4. Servicios de compra.

Puede establecer y mantener un saldo de cuenta para comprar los artículos que ofrecemos y vendemos en la Tienda virtual de Nintendo. Dicho saldo de cuenta se relaciona solamente con su Cuenta de red, está sujeto al saldo y los límites o restricciones de uso que imp]]></main_text><main_text index="6"><![CDATA[onemos periódicamente, y no se transfiere a terceros. Es posible que dicho saldo de cuenta no se use para comprar los artículos que ofrecen o venden otras personas, o que se venden fuera de la Tienda virtual de Nintendo. Sírvase consultar el Manual del usuario para obtener más información sobre las características de la Tienda virtual de Nintendo.

Usted es responsable de las compras, descargas, u otras adquisiciones de contenido que realice con su Cuenta de red en la Tienda virtual de Nintendo. Las compras en la Tienda virtual de Nintendo no son reembolsables ni transferibles a menos que se indique lo contrario en los términos publicados para una oferta específica o así lo requiera la ley. El Contenido digital no se vende. Este se obtiene mediante una licencia del Proveedor de contenidos, exclusivamente para su uso personal y no comercial en su Dispositivo Nintendo o según lo permitamos a través de los Servicios de red, en virtud de los términos del presente Acuerdo y cualquier término adicional publicado para el artículo de Contenido digital en la Tienda virtual de Nintendo, y sujetos a su pago por dicho Contenido digital. Las licencias de Contenido digital que se compran a través de su Cuenta de Nintendo y se descargan a un Dispositivo Nintendo pueden estar disponibles para su acceso y uso a través de otras Cuentas de Nintendo en dicho Dispositivo Nintendo.

La Tienda virtual de Nintendo puede apoyar otros Servicios de red, como por ejemplo los servicios que le permiten acceder, ver o descargar Contenido digital en su Dispositivo Nintendo; revisar otros artículos que pueden comprarse en relación con un Dispositivo Nintendo o los Servicios de Red; revisar su historia de compras o, si el Dispositivo Nintendo cuenta con esa función, usar los puntos para efectuar compras en la Tienda Wii durante la operación en modo compatible Wii.

5. Servicios de terceros.

No nos responsabilizamos por los Servicios de terceros que elija acceder o usar, y tampoco nos responsabilizamos por cualquier cobro u otra responsabilidad q]]></main_text><main_text index="7"><![CDATA[ue surja del uso de los Servicios de terceros. Nosotros no controlamos ni revisamos los Servicios de terceros, los cuales están sujetos a términos y condiciones de terceros distintos relacionados con dichos Servicios de terceros. La Política de privacidad de Nintendo no se aplica a los Servicios de terceros. Puede acceder y usar los Servicios de terceros únicamente bajo su propio riesgo.

6. Uso de la información.

Podemos recopilar, usar y divulgar información personal que (a) usted nos proporciona; (b) recopilamos automáticamente; y (c) recibimos de otras fuentes. Sírvase referirse a la Poítica de privacidad de Nintendo, ubicada en después del final de este Acuerdo, así como en Nintendo.com, para obtener mayor información sobre cómo recolectamos, usamos y desvelamos información de nuestros usuarios. La Política de privacidad de Nintendo se aplica a todos nuestros productos, servicios, sititos web, incluidos los Servicios de Red. Le recomendamos que revise la Política de privacidad de Nintendo antes de usar los Servicios de red o un Dispositivo o sitio web de Nintendo para ayudarlo a mantenerse informado sobre nuestras prácticas de privacidad.

7. Código de conducta.

Para ayudarnos a mantener los Servicios de red como un entorno amistoso y seguro para todos los usuarios, usted no deberá participar en actos de conducta perjudicial, ilegal o de otro modo ofensiva, como:

 A. Engañar, suplantar a otra persona, abusar, perseguir, amenazar o acosar a cualquier persona o compañía, como a otros usuarios, a la propia compañía o a sus empleados, representantes, moderadores o contratistas

 B. Cometer cualquier acto discriminatorio, difamatorio, de expresión de odio, de acoso, abusivo, obsceno, amenazante, físicamente peligroso o de otro modo objetable en relación con un Dispositivo Nintendo o los Servicios de red

 C. Hacer, distribuir, compartir o reproducir copias no autorizadas de juegos, música o imágenes en un Dispositivo Nintendo o los Servicios de red. ¡Esta es una actividad ilegal!

 D. Hacer nuevas versiones de]]></main_text><main_text index="8"><![CDATA[ Contenido digital o un Dispositivo Nintendo

 E. Intentar modificar u obtener acceso no autorizado al Dispositivo Nintendo o la Cuenta de red de otra persona, o intentar modificar, aplicar técnicas de ingeniería inversa, u obtener acceso no autorizado o de forma automatizada a cualquier computadora, hardware, software o red de Nintendo que se utilicen para proveer los Servicios de red o cualquier función de un Dispositivo Nintendo

 F. Hacer trampas en un juego, a menos que el Proveedor de contenidos haya habilitado dichas trampas de manera deliberada

 G. Alojar, interceptar, emular, aplicar técnicas de ingeniería inversa o redireccionar los protocolos de comunicaciones que Nintendo utiliza como parte de un Dispositivo Nintendo o los Servicios de red, cualquiera que sea el método utilizado para llevarlo a cabo; o hacer algo que pueda desviar o burlar medidas empleadas para impedir o limitar el acceso a cualquier área, contenido o código de cualquier Dispositivo Nintendo o Servicios de red (salvo que, de otra forma, lo permita la ley expresamente);

 H. Desarrollar cualquier aplicación de terceros que interactúe con el Contenido para el usuario y los Servicios de red sin nuestro consentimiento previo por escrito

 I. Participar en cualquier actividad comercial que implique el uso de un Dispositivo Nintendo o los Servicios de red, o en cualquier otra actividad que perturbe, disminuya la calidad o interfiera con la ejecución o impida la funcionalidad de un Dispositivo Nintendo, los Servicios de red u otros Servicios de terceros

 J. Usar cualquier robot, spider, crawler, scraper u otros medios automáticos o cualquier interfaz no provista por nosotros para acceder o extraer datos de cualquier Dispositivo Nintendo o Servicios de red

 K. Cargar, publicar, enviar por correo electrónico, transmitir o de otro modo poner a disposición de otros: (i) cualquier contenido o dato sobre los cuales usted no tenga derecho legal de poner a disposición de otros; (ii) cualquier contenido o dato que infrinjan cualquier patente, mar]]></main_text><main_text index="9"><![CDATA[ca registrada, secreto industrial, derecho de autor u otros derechos de propiedad intelectual o derechos de propiedad de cualquiera de las partes; (iii) cualquier material de publicidad o de promoción no solicitado o no autorizado; (iv) contenido o datos cuyo origen usted ha enmascarado; o (v) virus, datos corruptos u otros archivos destructivos, peligrosos o disruptivos (vi) contenido o datos que contengan información privada de cualquier tercero, incluidos, sin limitación, nombres, direcciones, correos electrónicos o información sobre tarjetas de crédito, o (vii) contenido o datos que sean obscenos, ilegales, o que incumplan con este Acuerdo o cuya publicación esté prohibida en su jurisdicción

8. Reserva de derechos e intereses.

Los Servicios de red le son proporcionados en virtud de una licencia limitada, mas no vendidos. Aparte de su licencia limitada para usar los Servicios de red según las disposiciones explícitas en este Acuerdo, nos reservamos todo derecho, título e interés relativo a los Servicios de red, incluidas, entre otras, todos los derechos de autor, patentes y marcas registradas relacionados, así como todos los demás derechos de propiedad o propiedad intelectual de cualquier tipo en cualquier país.

9. Descargo de responsabilidad de las garantías y limitación de responsabilidad.

EL USO DE LOS SERVICIOS DE RED Y LOS SERVICIOS DE TERCEROS ES POR SU PROPIA CUENTA Y RESPONSABILIDAD. NINGUNA INFORMACIÓN O ASESORÍA, VERBAL O POR ESCRITO, PROPORCIONADA POR NINTENDO O SUS REPRESENTANTES CREA UNA GARANTÍA. LOS SERVICIOS DE RED SE PROPORCIONAN "TAL CUAL" SIN GARANTÍAS DE NINGÚN TIPO. NINTENDO NIEGA TODA GARANTÍA CON RESPECTO A LOS SERVICIOS DE RED Y LOS SERVICIOS DE TERCEROS, EXPRESA O IMPLÍCITA, INCLUIDAS, ENTRE OTRAS, CUALQUIER GARANTÍA DE NO VIOLACIÓN DE DERECHOS DE TERCEROS, O LAS GARANTÍAS IMPLÍCITAS DE COMERCIABILIDAD E IDONEIDAD PARA UN PROPÓSITO EN PARTICULAR. HASTA DONDE LA LEY LO PERMITA, NINTENDO NO SE RESPONSABILIZARÁ ANTE USTED DE NINGÚN DAÑO DE NINGÚN TIPO, ESPECIAL O CONSECUENTE, QUE SURG]]></main_text><main_text index="10"><![CDATA[IERA DEL ACCESO, USO, MAL USO O INCAPACIDAD DE USO, POR PARTE SUYA, DE LOS SERVICIOS DE RED O CUALQUIER SERVICIO DE TERCEROS, O QUE ESTUVIERA RELACIONADO CON LOS MISMOS, INCLUSO EN LOS CASOS EN QUE SE HUBIERA NOTIFICADO A NINTENDO SOBRE LA POSIBILIDAD DE DICHO DAÑO. EN CUALQUIER CASO, LA RESPONSABILIDAD TOTAL DE NINTENDO ANTE USTED EN RELACIÓN CON CUALQUIER RECLAMO QUE SURGIERA DE LOS SERVICIOS DE RED Y LOS SERVICIOS DE TERCEROS, O QUE ESTUVIERA RELACIONADO CON LOS MISMOS, SE LIMITA A LA CANTIDAD REAL QUE USTED PAGÓ POR LOS SERVICIOS DE RED, QUE SON OBJETO DE DICHO RECLAMO. SI ALGUNA LEY RESTRINGE NUESTRA CAPACIDAD DE LIMITAR LA RESPONSABILIDAD O PRESENTAR EL DESCARGO DE RESPONSABILIDAD DE LAS GARANTÍAS, ES POSIBLE QUE LAS LIMITACIONES MENCIONADAS ANTERIORMENTE NO SE APLIQUEN A USTED. EN ESE CASO, LIMITAMOS NUESTRA RESPONSABILIDAD Y PRESENTAMOS EL DESCARGO DE RESPONSABILIDAD DE LAS GARANTÍAS HASTA DONDE LA LEY LO PERMITA COMO MÁXIMO.

10. Compensación.

Si nosotros o cualquiera de nuestras Filiales, concesionarios, entidades adjudicadoras o contratistas estuviéramos sujetos a cualquier reclamo, costo, daño, pérdida u otras responsabilidades, reales o probables, (en forma colectiva, "Pérdidas cubiertas") como resultado del uso por parte suya de cualquier Servicios de red, Contenido digital, un Dispositivo Nintendo o cualquier dato, información u otro artículo que usted ponga a disposición de otros por medio de los Servicios de red o un Dispositivo Nintendo, incluido el Contenido para el usuario, entonces usted acuerda otorgarnos a nosotros (y a nuestras filiales, concesionarios, entidades adjudicadoras, contratistas y empleados) una compensación por todas esas Pérdidas cubiertas y cualquier costo relacionado, como los honorarios razonables de abogados.

11. Comentarios.

Aparte del Contenido para el usuario, por lo general, puede enviar preguntas, comentarios, sugerencias, ideas, planes, notas, dibujos, materiales originales o creativos u otra información o material acerca de Nintendo y de los Servicios de red ("C]]></main_text><main_text index="11"><![CDATA[omentarios"). El comentario, ya sea enviado a través de los Servicios de red o de otra manera, no es confidencial y se convertirá en propiedad única de Nintendo. Nosotros tendremos los derechos exclusivos, incluidos todos los derechos de propiedad intelectual, para con dichos comentarios, y tendremos el derecho a la libre utilización y difusión de esta información para cualquier propósito, comercial o de otro tipo, sin reconocimiento ni compensación para usted.

12.	Resolución de controversias; Arbitraje vinculante de forma individual; Renuncia a tomar acciones colectivas.

 A. Nuestro departamento de servicio al consumidor está disponible para abordar cualquier inquietud que usted pueda tener sobre su Cuenta de red o los Servicios de red. Puede comunicarse con el departamento llamando al 1-800-255-3700, enviando un correo electrónico a useragreement@noa.nintendo.com o enviando un correo postal a Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: User Agreement, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052 USA. La mayor parte de los asuntos se resuelven rápidamente de esta manera a la satisfacción de nuestros clientes. Cualquier asunto que no podamos resolver y todas las controversias o reclamos que surgieran en virtud de este Acuerdo, o que estuvieran relacionados con el mismo, incluida su información, aplicabilidad, ejecución o incumplimiento (cada uno, un "Reclamo"), a excepción de los asuntos descritos en la Sección 12(C) a continuación, deberá resolverse finalmente por medio de arbitraje vinculante administrado por la Asociación de Arbitraje Estadounidense (American Arbitration Association, AAA) de conformidad con las disposiciones de sus Reglas de arbitraje comercial (Commercial Arbitration Rules) y los procedimientos complementarios para controversias relacionadas con el consumidor de la Asociación de Arbitraje Estadounidense (la "AAA"), con exclusión de cualquier regla o procedimiento que rija o permita acciones colectivas. El árbitro, y no cualquier tribunal ni entidad federal, estatal o local, deberá tener autoridad exclusiva par]]></main_text><main_text index="12"><![CDATA[a resolver todos los Reclamos. El árbitro deberá estar facultado para otorgar cualquier subsidio que estuviera disponible en un tribunal en virtud de la ley o en equidad. El fallo del árbitro deberá ser vinculante para todas las partes y puede presentarse como una sentencia ante cualquier tribunal con jurisdicción competente. Las partes entienden que, en ausencia de esta disposición obligatoria, tendrían el derecho de entablar una demanda ante un tribunal y tener un juicio ante un jurado. Además, entienden que, en ciertas circunstancias, los costos del arbitraje podrían exceder los costos del litigio y el derecho a intercambio de información prejudicial puede estar más limitado en arbitrajes que ante un tribunal. Las partes deberán realizar el arbitraje únicamente a título individual y no como una acción colectiva ni otra acción representativa; asimismo, las partes renuncian a su derecho de presentar una acción colectiva o buscar un subsidio con base en una acción colectiva. Si algún tribunal o arbitro determinan que la renuncia a la acción colectiva establecida en la oración anterior es nula o no es ejecutoria, por cualquier motivo, o que un arbitraje puede proceder con base en una acción colectiva, entonces la disposición del arbitraje establecida en esta Sección 13 deberá considerarse como nula en su totalidad y deberá considerarse que las partes no han acordado someter los Reclamos a arbitraje.

 B. Se puede acceder a las reglas que rigen el arbitraje visitando www.adr.org o llamando a la AAA al +1.800.778.7879. En la medida en que los honorarios de presentación inicial por el arbitraje excedan los honorarios de presentación inicial por una demanda, pagaremos la diferencia entre los honorarios. Si el árbitro decide que el arbitraje no carece de base legal, pagaremos todos los honorarios de la presentación efectiva y del árbitro por el arbitraje, siempre y cuando su reclamo sea menor a US$75 000. Las reglas del arbitraje también le permiten recuperar los honorarios de abogados en casos determinados.

 C. La Se]]></main_text><main_text index="13"><![CDATA[cción 12(A) no se aplica a ningún Reclamo (i) por el cual una de las partes intenta proteger sus derechos de propiedad intelectual (como su patente, derecho de autor, marca registrada, secreto industrial o derechos morales, sin incluir sus derechos de privacidad o publicidad), o (ii) que pueda presentarse ante un tribunal de reclamos menores.

 D. Derecho de exclusión de 30 días: Tiene derecho a excluirse de las disposiciones de esta Sección 12 por medio del envío de una notificación por escrito de su decisión de excluirse a la siguiente dirección: Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: CS Admin, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052 en un plazo de 30 días a partir de la creación de su Cuenta de red. Su notificación deberá incluir su número de cuenta. Si usted envía esta notificación, entonces la Sección 12 no se aplicará a ninguna de las partes. Si no envía esta notificación, entonces usted aceptar someterse a las disposiciones de esta Sección 12.

13.	General.

 A. Incumplimiento; rescisión; supervivencia. La rescisión de este Acuerdo será automática si usted no cumple con el mismo. En caso de dicha rescisión, usted debe cesar todo uso de los Servicios de red de inmediato. Las Secciones 3, 5, 6, 8, 9, 10, 12 y 13 del presente Acuerdo continuarán en vigor luego de cualquier rescisión de este tipo.

 B. Cambios en los Servicios de red; envío de los Servicios de red. Es posible que modifiquemos, cancelemos o suspendamos la disponibilidad de los Servicios de red en su totalidad o en parte, en cualquier momento, sin notificárselo. Es posible que involucremos a las Filiales o a terceros en el envío de los Servicios de red o en la ejecución de nuestras obligaciones en virtud del presente Acuerdo.

 C. Aplicación; sin derecho a renuncia; sin derecho a cesión. Si algún contenido del presente Acuerdo se considera inválido o no ejecutorio, dicho contenido no se aplicará más a las partes y se reemplazará con una disposición aplicable que refleje de forma más precisa la intención original de las partes; los demás contenidos del Acu]]></main_text><main_text index="14"><![CDATA[erdo continuarán en vigor, salvo se disponga lo contrario en el mismo. El incumplimiento por parte nuestra al no insistir en el estricto cumplimiento por parte suya del presente Acuerdo, o en la ejecución del mismo, no constituirá una renuncia a ninguno de nuestros derechos. No puede ceder sus derechos o intereses en virtud del presente Acuerdo a ninguna otra persona.

 D. Ley aplicable. Las leyes del estado de Washington, EE. UU., independientemente de la existencia de conflicto en sus disposiciones legales, regirá el presente Acuerdo y cualquier controversia de cualquier naturaleza que pudiera surgir entre usted y Nintendo.

 E. Lugar. Si la Sección 12 se considera inválida o no ejecutoria, entonces las partes consienten que la jurisdicción sea exclusiva de los tribunales ubicados en el Condado de King, Washington, EE. UU., para cualquier Reclamo.

 F. Inexistencia de terceros beneficiarios. Este acuerdo es para el beneficio de uno mismo, y será aplicado solo por las partes, y no tiene por objeto otorgar ningún derecho o beneficio a cualquier tercero, ni para crear obligaciones a ningún tercero.

 G. Cambios en los términos. Podríamos cambiar los términos del presente Acuerdo en cualquier momento sin aviso. Una versión actual del presente Acuerdo, que incluye cualquier cambio, se encuentra publicada en support.nintendo.com para su conveniencia. Si no está de acuerdo con ninguno de los cambios en el presente Acuerdo, debe anular su Cuenta de red y dejar de utilizar los Servicios de red.

 H. Notificaciones. Para ponerse en contacto con nuestro departamento de servicio al consumidor con respecto al presente Acuerdo, puede (i) enviar un correo electrónico a useragreement@noa.nintendo.com; (ii) enviar una carta a Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: User Agreement, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052 USA; o (iii) llamar al número gratuito 1-888-977-7627. Sus comunicaciones con nuestro departamento de servicio al consumidor no constituirá una notificación legal requerida por el presente Acuerdo o por la ley.

Para otros]]></main_text><main_text index="15"><![CDATA[ aspectos legales, debe contactarnos o notificarnos por escrito a: Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: General Counsel, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052.

Podemos notificarle sobre el presente Acuerdo a través de: (i) correo electrónico a la dirección asociada a su Cuenta de red; o (ii) por medio de mensajes publicados en la Tienda virtual de Nintendo, el sitio web de Nintendo, u otros sitios que le especifiquemos periódicamente. Estas notificaciones entrarán en vigencia a partir de la fecha de entrega o publicación. Asegúrese de mantener la dirección de correo electrónico asociado a su Cuenta de red actualizada.

 I. Notificaciones y procedimiento para realizar reclamos por violación del derecho de autor. Nintendo respeta la propiedad intelectual de otras personas y por ende solicitamos a los usuarios de productos y servicios de Nintendo que hagan lo mismo. Si siente que sus derechos de propiedad intelectual han sido violados, visítenos en la página www.nintendo.com/ippolicy para que lea toda nuestra política y presente una solicitud de retiro.

***Final del Acuerdo de Servicios de red de Nintendo***




Política de privacidad de Nintendo

Última actualización: 2 de julio de 2015

Nintendo sabe que la privacidad es importante para usted. Esta Política de privacidad describe de qué manera recopilamos, usamos, divulgamos, almacenamos y protegemos su información. Al usar un producto o servicio de Nintendo, usted acepta las prácticas descritas en esta Política de privacidad.

1. SU INFORMACIÓN

Información que usted nos proporciona. Recopilamos la información que usted nos proporciona al momento de utilizar nuestros productos y servicios, o en cualquier momento que se contacta con nosotros.

Algunos tipos de información que usted proporciona incluyen:

 * Información que debe proporcionar al momento de registrarse con la finalidad de utilizar nuestros servicios, que incluye su nombre, dirección, número de teléfono y dirección de correo electrónico;
 * Información que debe proporcionar al momento de iniciar sesión co]]></main_text><main_text index="16"><![CDATA[n la finalidad de acceder a nuestros servicios, que incluye su nombre de usuario y contraseña;
 * Información demográfica sobre usted, que incluye su edad, sexo, aficiones, intereses, y país de residencia;
 * Información de cualquier pago que realice, que incluye su número de tarjeta de crédito, fecha de caducidad y código de seguridad de la tarjeta de crédito, cuando sea necesario completar una transacción que haya iniciado;
 * Mensajes, fotos, videos, dibujos, grabaciones de audio y otros datos que comparta a través de las funciones interactivas de nuestros productos y servicios;
 * Correspondencia que nos envía directamente; e
 * Información que nos proporciona cuando no está en línea (por ejemplo, mediante el correo postal, formularios entregados en persona para participar en sorteos y transacciones de servicios para el consumidor, que incluyen reparaciones, pedidos de piezas y compras directas).

Información que recopilamos automáticamente. Recopilamos cierta información automáticamente cuando usted utiliza nuestros productos y servicios.

Algunos tipos de información que recopilamos automáticamente incluyen:

 * Información sobre el uso de nuestros productos, servicios y sitios web, incluidos el tipo de navegador, sistema operativo, plataforma, dirección IP, dirección MAC, idioma y región;
 * Información sobre los sitios web que visitó antes y después de visitar nuestros sitios web, consultas de búsqueda que lo llevaron a nuestros sitios web, consultas de búsqueda que realizó en nuestros sitios web; páginas y avisos que ha visto y enlaces en los que hizo clic al momento de utilizar nuestros sitios web;
 * Información sobre su dispositivo de Nintendo, incluidos el número de serie del dispositivo, la identificación del dispositivo, el punto de acceso inalámbrico y otra información técnica sobre su dispositivo; e
 * Información sobre su juego, estado en línea, uso de servicios en línea, amigos y códigos de amigos, compras, y otros datos acerca de sus interacciones con nuestros productos y servicios.

Informaci]]></main_text><main_text index="17"><![CDATA[ón que recibimos de otras fuentes. Podemos recibir información sobre usted desde otras fuentes, ya sea a través de servicios de terceros y minoristas.

Algunos ejemplos de información que podemos recibir de otras fuentes incluyen:

 * Datos de navegación, que incluyen sitios web visitados y avisos vistos o en los que hizo clic;
 * Información sobre operaciones relacionadas con el servicio al consumidor; e
 * Información de fecha de compra.

Tenga en cuenta que podemos añadir la información que recibimos de otras fuentes a la información que ya tenemos sobre usted. También podemos combinar su información con la información sobre otros usuarios, que incluye información de juegos, demográfica, de término de búsqueda, de secuencias de clics y de compras; y utilizar esta información combinada en un formato agregado.


2. COOKIES, BALIZAS WEB, ARCHIVOS DE REGISTROS Y SOCIOS EXTERNOS

Para recopilar parte de la información descrita anteriormente, podemos utilizar balizas web, cookies, archivos de registro y tecnologías similares en algunos de nuestros productos y servicios, incluidos nuestros mensajes de correo electrónico.

 * Balizas web: Podemos utilizar balizas web (también conocidas como rastreadores de píxel o GIF invisibles), que son pequeñas imágenes gráficas colocadas en una página web, un documento web o un mensaje de correo electrónico. Las balizas web se diseñan para recopilar cierta información del usuario y controlar ciertas actividades del mismo. La información recopilada por las balizas web podría incluir su dirección IP, dirección MAC, dirección URL de la página de donde usted viene, o su interacción con nuestro sitio web, o un mensaje de correo electrónico que le enviamos. Podemos utilizar la información recopilada a través de las balizas web, por ejemplo, para determinar la forma de mejorar ciertos productos y servicios mediante la identificación de páginas web, servicios, funciones y productos más populares; así como para personalizar nuestros productos y servicios; realizar recomendaciones de produc]]></main_text><main_text index="18"><![CDATA[tos y servicios; y completar operaciones que usted haya solicitado.
 * Cookies: Podemos usar las cookies, que son identificadores únicos que, a veces, se colocan en su dispositivo para grabar los datos acerca de sus visitas a un sitio web, de modo que el sitio pueda reconocer su dispositivo y personalizar su visita. La información recopilada por las cookies puede estar vinculada a su historial de operaciones, juegos en línea u otra información. Podemos utilizar la información recopilada por las cookies, por ejemplo, para determinar la forma de mejorar ciertos productos y servicios mediante la identificación de las páginas web, servicios, funciones y productos más populares; así como para personalizar nuestros productos y servicios; realizar recomendaciones de productos y servicios; y completar operaciones que usted haya solicitado. Usted puede configurar ciertos navegadores para rechazar las cookies o para que le indiquen cuando le han enviado una cookie. Sin embargo, no utilizar las cookies podría evitar que usted tenga acceso a ciertas funciones y características de nuestros productos y servicios.
 * Archivos de registro: Nosotros conservamos archivos de registro que registran la actividad relacionada con el uso de nuestros productos y servicios, como el número de visitas que una página web ha recibido en particular, el tipo y la calidad de la conexión a internet de un usuario, el tipo de hardware y/o software utilizado para acceder a un servicio en particular, las funciones usadas de un servicio y su frecuencia de uso. Las entradas dentro de estos archivos de registro podrían incluir, por ejemplo, direcciones IP, direcciones MAC, información de cookies, identificación de dispositivo, datos de operaciones, configuración de dispositivo y actividad de descarga. Podemos usar estos archivos de registro, por ejemplo, para controlar el tráfico en nuestro sitio web, facilitar la utilización de determinados servicios y solucionar problemas técnicos.
 * Socios externos: También podemos permitir a nuestros socios externo]]></main_text><main_text index="19"><![CDATA[s establecer las cookies, balizas web y tecnologías similares en nuestros sitios web, o dentro de los mensajes de correo electrónico enviados en nuestra representación, para ayudarnos a ejecutar diversas funciones internas necesarias para operar nuestro negocio. Estos terceros también pueden utilizar las cookies y balizas web, y otras tecnologías para recopilar información acerca de sus visitas a nuestros sitios web y a otros lugares del internet y pueden utilizar esa información durante o después de sus visitas a nuestros sitios web para proporcionarle anuncios a lo largo de todo el internet sobre productos y servicios que podrían ser de interés para usted. Algunos de estos terceros pueden ofrecerle una manera de excluir este tipo de publicidad dirigida a través de mecanismos de selección de la industria. Para obtener más información sobre terceros que participan en este tipo de ofertas selectivas y sobre como ejercer las opciones que podrían estar disponibles para usted, puede visitar www.networkadvertising.org y www.aboutads.info.

3. USO DE LA INFORMACIÓN

Podemos usar su información para nuestras compañías afiliadas o socios externos con el fin de: (i) cumplir con sus solicitudes de productos, servicios e información, lo que incluye enviarle mensajes comerciales y no comerciales, y completar los pedidos que haya realizado; (ii) informarle sobre nuestros productos, servicios y sitios web, lo que incluye enviarle publicidad y materiales de promoción; (iii) facilitarle el uso de nuestros productos y servicios; (iv) permitirle participar en juegos en línea, concursos, sorteos, encuestas, foros públicos y otras funciones que se le proporciona mediante nuestros productos, servicios y sitios web; (v) formular recomendaciones y personalizar el contenido, las funciones y publicidad disponible mediante nuestros productos, servicios y sitios web y en los sitios web de otros; (vi) preparar pedidos de reparación y responder a otras consultas del servicio al cliente; (vii) proporcionar servicios de interfaz del administra]]></main_text><main_text index="20"><![CDATA[dor, lo que incluye actualizaciones de sistema, mensajes de sistema; (viii) proporcionar juegos gratis, aplicaciones, pruebas y otros contenidos; (ix) analizar y facilitar el uso de nuestros productos, servicios y sitios web; (x) facilitar estudios demográficos; (xi) comprender, mejorar y desarrollar nuestros productos, servicios y sitios web; (xii) evitar actividades potencialmente ilegales u ofensivas; (xiii) hacer cumplir nuestros derechos y el de nuestros usuarios; (xiv) verificar su identidad y evitar transacciones fraudulentas; y (xv) para otros fines que se le informen en el momento en que recopilemos su información o para los cuales usted haya dado su consentimiento.

4. DIVULGACIÓN DE LA INFORMACIÓN

En ocasiones, podemos hacer que cierta información que se haya recopilado esté disponible para nuestras compañías afiliadas, socios externos, otros usuarios de Nintendo, el público en general y para otros fines legales y comerciales. Por ejemplo:

 * Compañías afiliadas a Nintendo. Podemos compartir información con otras compañías afiliadas a Nintendo que la usen conforme con esta Política de privacidad.
 * Terceros. Podemos compartir información con nuestros socios externos para ayudarnos a realizar diversas funciones necesarias para dirigir nuestros negocios o cumplir con nuestras solicitudes (por ejemplo, para ayudarle a procesar sus descargas o compras, y desarrollar y llevar a cabo campañas de publicidad). Además, podemos compartir dicha información; por ejemplo, con el fin de completar sus operaciones, enviarle publicidad y otros materiales de promoción, y brindar asistencia en la creación de cuentas de usuarios con terceros.
 * Otros usuarios y amigos. Podemos compartir información, lo que incluye, por ejemplo, su nombre de usuario, información del perfil Mii, estados en línea, saludos Mii y otra información sobre el juego, con otros usuarios de Nintendo cuando use las funciones en línea de nuestros productos y servicios.
 * Público en general. Cuando usa algunos de nuestros servicios en línea, por ej]]></main_text><main_text index="21"><![CDATA[emplo, cuando juega en línea o publica algo en Miiverse, su nombre de usuario, apodo, perfil de usuario y cierta información de su juego pueden aparecer en internet y ser vistos por el público en general.
 * Comunicación local. Algunos dispositivos de Nintendo tienen funciones de comunicación local que usted puede activar. Estas funciones permiten que nosotros y otros usuarios de Nintendo podamos recopilar y compartir automáticamente alguna información. Estas funciones también permiten a otros usuarios de Nintendo y a nosotros comunicarnos e interactuar con usted de manera automática. Al activar estas funciones, puede recibir información sobre, y comunicación de, otros usuarios de Nintendo; además, puede recibir publicidad y materiales de promoción de Nintendo y sus socios externos. Puede desactivar estas funciones de comunicación local en cualquier momento mediante las configuraciones del sistema de su dispositivo de Nintendo.
 * Objetivos comerciales y legales. Podemos divulgar su información para cumplir con el proceso legal, responder reclamaciones o consultas, o proteger los derechos de propiedad o seguridad personal de Nintendo, de nuestros usuarios o el público en general. También se puede divulgar su información como parte de cualquier venta o transferencia de las acciones de la compañía, si se autoriza legalmente.

Usted es responsable de cualquier información que comparta con otros mediante el uso de nuestros productos, servicios y sitios web. Sea consciente de que otros usuarios pueden almacenar, modificar o compartir con terceros, la información que usted les emite.

5. CUENTAS VINCULADAS

Le ofrecemos una cuenta para uno más de nuestros programas de fidelidad, que incluye el Club Nintendo, para que usted tenga la oportunidad de recibir contenido personalizado y participar en una variedad de actividades, promociones y programas. Dentro de ciertos parámetros, usted podrá vincular su dispositivo o cuenta de red de Nintendo a su cuenta de fidelidad. En algunos casos, utilizaremos su información para, por]]></main_text><main_text index="22"><![CDATA[ ejemplo, registrar automáticamente sus compras en su cuenta de fidelidad para que pueda recibir recompensas y promociones. Puede desconectarse de estas cuentas en la sección de configuración de Nintendo eShop.

6. TERCEROS

Puede revelar su información a terceros cuando utilice nuestros productos y servicios con la finalidad de jugar con terceros, usar aplicaciones o plugins y ver anuncios o visitar sitios web de terceros. No somos responsables de las prácticas de privacidad ofrecidas por terceros y le recomendamos que revise sus políticas de privacidad antes de enviar cualquier información.

7. ADVERTENCIA PARA PADRES O TUTORES LEGALES: PROTEGER LA PRIVACIDAD DE LOS MENORES

Según las leyes aplicables, obtenemos el consentimiento de los padres para recopilar la información personal de sus hijos. Puede encontrar información relacionada con la recopilación, uso y divulgación de información personal de nuestros usuarios, que incluye menores de 13 años, en las secciones indicadas anteriormente que se titulan SU INFORMACIÓN, USO DE LA INFORMACIÓN, DIVULGACIÓN DE LA INFORMACIÓN.

Usted puede revisar, y hacer que se borre, la información personal que recopilamos de su menor hijo, y, a su vez, puede rehusar permitir nuestra recopilación futura o utilizar la información personal del menor contactando al Administrador de privacidad de Nintendo vía correo electrónico a privacypolicy@noa.nintendo.com, o por teléfono al 1-888-977-7627, o mediante un correo postal a Nintendo of America Inc., Atención: Nintendo Privacy Administrator, 4600 150th Avenue NE, Redmond, WA 98052, USA. Antes de responder su solicitud de revisar la información personal recopilada de su menor hijo, le solicitaremos que siga los procedimientos relacionados para ayudar a verificar su identidad como padre o tutor legal del menor. Podemos rehusar cualquier solicitud que no siga estos procedimientos. Si elige hacer que se borre la información del menor, rehúsa permitir la recopilación futura o utilizar la información del menor, es probable que algunas func]]></main_text><main_text index="23"><![CDATA[iones de nuestros productos y servicios estén limitadas o no disponibles.

Tenga en cuenta que los editores de los juegos de terceros, proveedores de aplicaciones y proveedores de contenido pueden recopilar, utilizar y divulgar la información personal del menor a través de nuestros productos y servicios cuando su hijo utilice el contenido o servicios de terceros. Nintendo no se responsabiliza por las prácticas de privacidad de terceros y recomendamos que usted revise sus políticas de privacidad antes de que el menor brinde o intercambie cualquier información personal en el contenido y servicios de terceros.

Recomendamos encarecidamente que supervise al menor en cuanto al uso de los productos y servicios en todo momento. Puede restringirle el uso de ciertas funciones de nuestros productos y servicios mediante el control parental de configuración en su dispositivo de Nintendo. Para una descripción detallada de estas funciones de control parental, vea el manual del usuario de su dispositivo de Nintendo.

8. SEGURIDAD

Nintendo adopta medidas razonables, y ha establecido garantías razonables para proteger su información contra pérdida, robo, uso indebido y acceso no autorizado, divulgación, alteración y destrucción. Usted debe comprender que no podemos garantizar que el sistema de almacenamiento de datos o transmisión de datos a través de internet o cualquier otra red pública sea 100 % segura.

Tenga en cuenta que la información recopilada por terceros no puede tener las mismas protecciones de seguridad como la información que nos envía o que recopilamos, y no nos responsabilizamos por la protección de la seguridad de dicha información.

Si instala aplicaciones o contenidos no autorizados, o realiza modificaciones no autorizadas a su dispositivo de Nintendo o su software, su información puede verse comprometida. Nintendo no se responsabiliza por cualquier recopilación, uso o divulgación de información de cualquier dispositivo de Nintendo que tenga modificaciones no autorizadas, o contenga software o contenido no aut]]></main_text><main_text index="24"><![CDATA[orizado.

9. OPCIÓN DE EXCLUSIÓN

Puede usar un dispositivo de Nintendo sin que nos proporcione información; sin embargo, algunas funciones y aplicaciones no estarían disponibles para usted. Usted puede optar por evitar la recopilación de determinada información simplemente con no utilizar nuestros servicios. También puede cancelar ciertos tipos de recopilación de información a través de la configuración de su dispositivo de Nintendo, controles parentales u otros mecanismos de cancelación que ponemos a su disposición. Es posible que cierta información técnica agregada sobre su Nintendo sea recopilada automáticamente cuando usted, u otro usuario de su dispositivo se conecte a internet. Puede optar por no recibir correos electrónicos comerciales por parte de Nintendo siguiendo las instrucciones contenidas en dichos correos.

10. ELIMINACIÓN DE INFORMACIÓN ALMACENADA EN SU DISPOSITIVO DE NINTENDO

Cierta información personal puede estar almacenada en su dispositivo de Nintendo. Para su protección, antes de venderlo, transferirlo o realizar otra acción con su dispositivo de Nintendo, por favor, elimine toda la información almacenada, incluyendo la información almacenada en cualquiera de los accesorios del dispositivo. Para obtener instrucciones sobre cómo eliminar la información almacenada en su dispositivo de Nintendo, consulte el manual de usuario o visite support.nintendo.com.
Si transfiere datos desde un dispositivo de Nintendo a otro, utilizando cualquiera de nuestras herramientas o funciones del sistema de transferencia, cualquier información personal que se encuentre almacenada en el dispositivo se transferirá como parte del proceso.

11. USUARIOS INTERNACIONALES

Toda información que usted proporciona o que se recopila a través del uso de nuestros productos, servicios o sitios web, puede almacenarse, procesarse y transferirse dentro y hacia los Estados Unidos o en cualquier otro país donde nosotros o nuestras empresas afiliadas o socios externos contemos con instalaciones. Por lo tanto, las autoridades gubern]]></main_text><main_text index="25"><![CDATA[amentales extranjeras pueden tener acceso a su información conforme a las leyes locales aplicables. Al usar cualquiera de nuestros sitios web establecidos en EE. UU., o al designar a los Estados Unidos como la región para su dispositivo Nintendo, usted da su consentimiento para que se recopile, almacene, procese y transfiera información dentro y hacia los Estados Unidos u otros países o territorios de acuerdo con lo establecido por las leyes de Estados Unidos. Cumplimos con los Principios de Puerto Seguro de los EE. UU y la UE y los Principios del Puerto Seguro de los EE. UU. y Suiza (Safe Harbor) establecidos por el Departamento de Comercio de los Estados Unidos en cuanto a la recopilación, el uso y la retención de datos provenientes del Espacio Económico Europeo y Suiza. Para obtener más información sobre los principios de puerto seguro, consulte la página web del Departamento de Comercio de los Estados Unidos.

12. CAMBIOS EN LA POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD

Podemos actualizar esta Política de privacidad periódicamente. Cuando actualicemos esta Política de privacidad, revisaremos la "última fecha de actualización" mencionada anteriormente. Las actualizaciones serán publicadas en support.nintendo.com. Le recomendamos que revise la Política de privacidad cada vez que utilice nuestros productos, servicios o sitios web para que se mantenga informado sobre nuestras prácticas de privacidad.

13. CERTIFICACIÓN ESRB

Esta Política de privacidad y el sello de certificación ubicado en nuestra página web confirma que somos un concesionario válido y miembro participante del Programa en línea de privacidad certificado de la Junta de Clasificación de Software de Entretenimiento (ESRB): Privacidad en línea de ESRB. Para ayudarlo a proteger su privacidad, hemos realizado voluntariamente esta iniciativa de privacidad. Como concesionario de este programa de certificación de privacidad, nuestras páginas webs, otras aplicaciones y mecanismos de rendición de cuentas que administra ESRB de manera independiente, se someten a constantes au]]></main_text><main_text index="26"><![CDATA[ditorías. ESRB ha revisado y certificado que todos nuestros sitios web que cuentan con el sello de certificación de ESRB cumplen con las prácticas establecidas sobre el uso y la recopilación de información en línea.

14. CONTÁCTENOS SI TIENE PREGUNTAS, COMENTARIOS O INQUIETUDES SOBRE LA PRIVACIDAD

Si tiene alguna pregunta, reclamaciones o comentarios sobre esta Política de privacidad, o sobre cualquiera de nuestras prácticas de privacidad, comuníquese con el Administrador de privacidad de Nintendo por correo electrónico a privacypolicy@noa.nintendo.com, por teléfono al 1-888-977-7627, o por correo postal a Nintendo of America Inc., a la atención de: Privacy Administrator, 4600 150th Avenue NE, Redmond, WA 98052, EE. UU.

También puede comunicarse con ESRB Privacy Certified por correo electrónico a privacy@esrb.org o por correo normal a ESRB Privacy Certified, Attn: Privacy Certified Program, 420 Lexington Avenue, Suite 2024, New York, NY 10017.
]]></main_text></texts><type>NINTENDO-NETWORK-EULA</type><version>0300</version></agreement><agreement><country>AG</country><language>fr</language><language_name>Français</language_name><publish_date>2014-09-29T20:07:36</publish_date><texts xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="chunkedStoredAgreementText"><agree_text><![CDATA[J'accepte]]></agree_text><main_title><![CDATA[Contrat d'utilisation des services en ligne]]></main_title><non_agree_text><![CDATA[Je n'accepte pas]]></non_agree_text><main_text index="1"><![CDATA[Accord de Services En Ligne Nintendo

LA PRÉSENTE CONSTITUE UN IMPORTANT CONTRAT QUI S’APPLIQUE À VOTRE UTILISATION DES SERVICES EN LIGNE! VEUILLEZ FAIRE DÉFILER VERS LE BAS!

Si vous avez moins de 18 ans, ARRÊTEZ!

Votre parent ou tuteur légal doit lire et accepter ce contrat.

Accord de Services En Ligne Nintendo

Dernière mise à jour : 29 septembre 2014

La présente constitue un contrat entre vous et Nintendo of America Inc. (avec ses Affiliés « Nintendo » ou « nous » ou « notre » ou « nos ») qui décrit vos droits d’utilisation des Services en Ligne. Lorsque vous utilisez les Services en Ligne, vous devez respecter l’Accord de Services En Ligne, et toutes les autres règles, politiques et avis applicables affichés sur le site Web de Nintendo ou sur Nintendo eShop (collectivement, le « Contrat »). En utilisant ou en accédant aux Services en Ligne ou en acceptant de respecter le présent Contrat sur l’interface utilisateur d’un Appareil Nintendo, vous acceptez d’être lié par les conditions de ce Contrat. Veuillez lire le présent Contrat attentivement. Si vous n’acceptez pas les conditions du présent Contrat, vous n’êtes autorisé à utiliser ni les Service en Ligne.

Aux fins du présent Contrat :

 « Affiliés » signifie les entités qui contrôlent, sont contrôlées ou exercent un contrôle conjoint avec Nintendo of America Inc.;

 « Fournisseur de Contenu » signifie la partie qui accorde une licence de Contenu Numérique, qui peut être nous, un tiers fournisseur d’applications, ou un tiers éditeur de jeux;

 « Contenu Numérique » signifie un contenu électronique numérisé mis à votre disposition par l’entremise des Services en Ligne ou qui est compatible avec et autorisé par nous pour une utilisation en rapport avec les Services en Ligne, comme les jeux, les vidéos, la musique, les images, le texte, les applications, et toute mise à jour, remplacement ou contenu supplémentaire en liaison avec ce qui précède;

 « Compte Réseau » signifie un compte que vous créez et maintenez pour votre utilisation des Services en Ligne te]]></main_text><main_text index="2"><![CDATA[l que permis aux présentes et qui nécessite un compte;

 « Services en Ligne » signifie ces services que nous vous offrons de temps en temps, par l’entremise d’un Appareil Nintendo, d’un ordinateur personnel, d’autres appareils autorisées par Nintendo ou en ligne, ce qui comprend sans s’y limiter, Nintendo eShop, l’accès au ou la livraison de Contenu Numérique ou de logiciels, d’applications, de services de soutien, l’accès aux Services de Tierces Parties, et l’accès à ou l’utilisation d’un Compte Réseau ou d’information, de données, ou d’autres matériaux en lien avec ce qui précède, et toutes les conditions additionnelles sous lesquelles chacun des éléments qui précèdent sont fournis;

 « Appareil Nintendo » signifie un appareil de marque Nintendo que nous autorisons pour utilisation avec les Services en Ligne;

 « Nintendo eShop » signifie les services d’achat que nous rendons disponibles dans le cadre de Services en Ligne auxquels nous pouvons accéder par l’entremise d’un Appareil Nintendo (ou d’autres appareils et méthodes, quels qu’ils soient, que nous autorisons pour un tel accès) pour l’achat, ou l’acquisition de toute autre manière, d’une licence de Contenu Numérique et pour l’achat d’autres articles que nous offrons de temps en temps;

 « Site Web Nintendo » signifie nos sites Web, y compris ceux dont les pages d’accueil sont situées au www.nintendo.com et au www.nintendo.net;

 « Services de Tierces Parties » signifie les services, applications, logiciels, et données rendus disponibles par les tierces parties par les Services en Ligne;

 « Contenu Utilisateur » signifie le texte, les images, l’audio, les vidéos, les critiques ou autre contenu créés par vous ou pour l’utilisation desquels une licence vous est accordée, et auquel le grand public et les autres utilisateurs des Services en Ligne peuvent accéder et qu’ils peuvent visionner; et

 « Manuel de l’Utilisateur » signifie les manuels d’information que nous mettons à votre disposition sur votre Appareil Nintendo et au support.nintendo.com, ou que no]]></main_text><main_text index="3"><![CDATA[us rendons accessible pour vous par les Services en Ligne ou par quelque autre méthode que ce soit, y compris toute mise à jour de ces manuels que nous pourrions afficher de temps en temps.

1. Services en Ligne.

Nintendo vous accorde une licence personnelle, non exclusive, non transférable et révocable, sous réserve des dispositions du présent Contrat, pour l’utilisation des Services en Ligne dans le cadre du présent Contrat, uniquement sur une base non commerciale. Vous êtes responsable de tout frais ou autres charges qui découlent de votre utilisation des Services en Ligne, comme les frais associés à l’utilisation de Nintendo eShop ou de Services de Tierces Parties.

Les Services en Ligne ne peuvent être utilisés qu’à l’intérieur des États-Unis, du Canada et de certains autres pays situés dans les Amériques. Les Services en Ligne peuvent ne pas être fonctionnels à l’extérieur de ces pays. En utilisant les Services en Ligne à l’extérieur de ces pays, ou en désignant l’un de ces pays comme votre région sur un Appareil Nintendo ou sur le site Web de Nintendo, vous acceptez d’être lié par les Conditions de ce Contrat. Certains des Services en Ligne peuvent ne pas vous être disponibles en raison des limitations légales ou techniques des réglages de votre Appareil Nintendo. Veuillez consulter le Manuel de l’Utilisateur pour plus de renseignements concernant la configuration et l’utilisation des Services en Ligne qui vous sont disponibles.

Les Services en Ligne pourraient vous permettre de transférer une partie ou la totalité de vos données, information, soldes de compte et Contenu Numérique entre Appareils Nintendo dont vous êtes le propriétaire ou entre vos Comptes Réseau. Veuillez consulter le Manuel de l’Utilisateur pour de plus amples renseignements sur cette fonction.

2. Votre Compte Réseau.

Un Compte Réseau peut être requis pour l’utilisation de certains Services en Ligne. Lors de la création de votre Compte Réseau, vous devez fournir des informations complètes et précises, et mettre à jour ces information]]></main_text><main_text index="4"><![CDATA[s au besoin.

Le consentement parental est requis pour la création d’un Compte Réseau et pour l’utilisation des Services en Ligne par un enfant de moins de 13 ans. Les instructions pour le consentement parental seront fournies lors du processus de configuration du Compte Réseau. Veuillez consulter la Politique de Confidentialité de Nintendo qui suit le présent contrat sur un Appareil Nintendo, ainsi que Nintendo.com pour obtenir plus de détails sur nos pratiques relatives à la confidentialité.

Votre Compte Réseau vous est personnel. Vous ne pouvez pas transférer, céder ou vendre votre Compte Réseau à autrui. Vous devriez protéger votre Compte Réseau contre l’accès non autorisé ou l’utilisation par d’autres, par exemple en conservant votre mot de passe de Compte Réseau dans un endroit sûr. Veuillez nous faire savoir immédiatement si vous êtes témoin d’un accès ou d’une utilisation non autorisés de votre Compte Réseau. Enlevez toute information liée à votre Compte Réseau de votre Appareil Nintendo avant de vendre, transférer ou partager votre Appareil Nintendo avec autrui. Veuillez consulter le Manuel de l’Utilisateur pour les instructions relativement au retrait d’information.

Vous êtes responsable de vous assurer que votre Compte Réseau soit utilisé, soit par vous soit par autrui, uniquement tel qu’il est permis de le faire selon ce Contrat. Cela comprend l’utilisation de votre Compte Réseau pour accéder aux Services en Ligne ou utiliser ces derniers. L’utilisation de votre Compte Réseau en violation du présent Contrat pourrait entraîner la suspension ou la suppression de votre Compte Réseau ainsi que votre capacité d’utiliser les Services en Ligne, et pourrait également entraîner la résiliation de ce Contrat.

Vous pouvez annuler votre Compte Réseau en tout temps. Si vous annulez votre Compte Réseau, vous ne pourrez plus accéder aux données, à l’information ou au solde associé à votre Compte Réseau. Veuillez consulter le Manuel de l’Utilisateur pour des renseignements relativement à l’annulation de votre Compt]]></main_text><main_text index="5"><![CDATA[e Réseau ainsi que d’autres renseignements.

3. Contenu d’Utilisateur.

Votre Contenu d’Utilisateur vous appartient. Cependant, en participant au présent Contrat, vous accordez à Nintendo une licence mondiale, libre de droits, irrévocable, perpétuelle, non exclusive et pouvant donner lieu à l’octroi d’une sous-licence pour l’utilisation, la reproduction, la modification, l’adaptation, la publication, la traduction, la distribution et l’affichage du Contenu d’Utilisateur que vous publiez ou fournissez, en tout ou en partie, et pour l’incorporation de votre Contenu d’Utilisateur à d’autres projets, quelle qu’en soit la forme, médias ou technologies connues ou développés ultérieurement, y compris aux fins de promotion et de marketing.

Nintendo n’assume aucune responsabilité pour tout Contenu d’Utilisateur publié, stocké, téléchargé par vous ou par une tierce partie, ni pour quelque perte ou quelques dommages que ce soit à cet égard. Nintendo n’est pas non plus responsable des erreurs, diffamations, diffamations verbales, omissions, mensonges, obscénités, pornographie ou profanités que vous pourriez rencontrer. Vous utilisez l’Appareil Nintendo et les Services en Ligne à vos propres risques. En tant que fournisseur de services interactifs, Nintendo n’est pas responsable des déclarations, des assertions ou du Contenu d’Utilisateur créé par ses utilisateurs.

Vous consentez et acceptez que Nintendo puisse accéder, de surveiller, utiliser, divulguer ou conserver des renseignements relatifs à votre utilisation des Services en Ligne, y compris mais sans s’y limiter, vos renseignements et Contenu d’Utilisateur, ou de l’information que Nintendo obtient en suivant votre utilisation d’un Appareil Nintendo ou du Service en Ligne lorsque Nintendo croit de bonne foi qu’il est nécessaire de le faire afin : (a) de respecter les lois applicables et de répondre aux autorités compétentes dans le cadre d’un acte de procédure; (b) de faire respecter le présent Contrat ou de protéger les droits ou les biens de Nintendo, ses utilisateur]]></main_text><main_text index="6"><![CDATA[s, ou le public; (c) de contribuer à prévenir la mort ou des blessures sérieuses; ou (d) prévenir les éventuelles activités illicites ou offensantes.

4. Services d’achat.

Vous pouvez établir et maintenir un solde de compte pour l’achat d’articles que nous offrons et vendons dans Nintendo eShop. Ce solde de compte est associé uniquement avec votre Compte Réseau, est assujetti aux limites de solde, ou d’utilisation ou de restrictions que nous pourrions imposer de temps en temps, et ne peut être transféré vers des tierces parties. Ce solde de compte ne peut être utilisé pour l’achat d’articles offerts ou vendus par d’autres à l’extérieur de Nintendo eShop. Veuillez consulter le Manuel de l’Utilisateur pour de plus amples renseignements sur les fonctionnalités de Nintendo eShop.

Vous êtes responsable de tout achat, téléchargement et de toute autre acquisition de contenu effectué avec votre Compte Réseau dans Nintendo eShop. Les achats effectués dans Nintendo eShop sont non remboursables et non transférables sauf disposition contraire affichée relativement à une offre particulière ou requise par la loi. Le Contenu Numérique est autorisé sous licence, et non vendu, et vous est octroyé par le Fournisseur de Contenu, uniquement pour votre utilisation personnelle et non commerciale sur votre Appareil Nintendo ou tel que nous le permettons par l’entremise des Services en Ligne, soumis aux conditions de ce Contrat et à toute autre condition affichée relativement à cet item de Contenu Numérique dans Nintendo eShop et sous réserve de votre paiement complet relativement à ce Contenu Numérique. Les licences de Contenu Numérique qui sont achetées par l’entremise de votre Compte Nintendo et téléchargées à un Appareil Nintendo pourraient être disponibles pour l’accès et l’utilisation par l’entremise d’autres Comptes Nintendo sur cet Appareil Nintendo.

Nintendo eShop peut prendre en charge d’autres Services en Ligne, tels que les services qui vous permettent d’accéder, de visionner ou de télécharger du Contenu Numérique sur vot]]></main_text><main_text index="7"><![CDATA[re Appareil Nintendo, pour examiner d’autres items qui peuvent être achetés en lien avec un Appareil Nintendo ou les Services en Ligne, pour examiner votre historique d’achats ou, si cette fonctionnalité est prise en charge par votre Appareil Nintendo, pour utiliser des points pour effectuer des achats dans la boutique Wii en fonctionnement en mode compatible avec la console Wii.

5. Services de Tierces Parties.

Nous ne sommes pas responsables des Services de Tierces Parties que vous choisissez pour l’accès ou l’utilisation, et nous ne sommes pas responsables des frais ou autres responsabilités découlant de votre utilisation des Services de Tierces Parties. Les Services de Tierces Parties ne sont ni examinés, ni suivis par nous et sont soumis à des modalités générales de tierces parties distinctes associées à de tels Services de Tierces Parties. La Politique de Confidentialité de Nintendo ne s’applique pas aux Services de Tierces Parties. Vous accédez et utilisez des Services de Tierces Parties uniquement à vos propres risques.

6. Utilisation des informations.

Nous pourrions recueillir, utiliser et divulguer des informations personnelles que (a) vous nous fournissez; (b) nous recueillons automatiquement; et (c) nous recevons d’autres sources. Veuillez consulter la Politique de Confidentialité de Nintendo figurant à la fin du présent Contrat et aussi accessible sur Nintendo.com pour savoir comment nous recueillons, utilisons et divulguons les informations de nos utilisateurs. La Politique de Confidentialité s’applique à tous les produits, services et sites Web, y compris les Services en Ligne. Nous vous recommandons d’examiner la Politique de Confidentialité de Nintendo avant chaque utilisation des Services en Ligne ou d’un Appareil ou du site Web Nintendo afin de vous tenir informé de nos pratiques en matière de confidentialité.

7. Code de conduite.

Afin d’aider à maintenir les Services en Ligne sûrs et sécuritaires pour tous les usagers, vous ne vous engagerez pas dans un comportement nuisible, illégal ou o]]></main_text><main_text index="8"><![CDATA[ffensant, tel que :

 A. Déguiser l’identité, usurper l’identité, abuser, traquer, menacer ou harceler toute personne ou société, tel que d’autres utilisateurs, nous ou nos employés, représentants, modérateurs ou entrepreneurs;

 B. Se livrer à une conduite discriminatoire, diffamatoire, haineuse, harcelante, abusive, obscène, menaçante, physiquement dangereuse ou répréhensible en lien avec un Appareil Nintendo ou les Services en Ligne;

 C. Produire, disséminer, partager ou jouer des copies non autorisées de jeux, de musique, ou d’images sur un Appareil Nintendo ou sur les Services en Ligne; cela constitue une activité illégale!

 D. Produire de nouvelles versions d’un Contenu Numérique ou d’un Appareil Nintendo;

 E. Tenter de modifier ou d’accéder d’une manière non autorisée à l’Appareil Nintendo ou au Compte Réseau d’autrui ou tenter de modifier, d’utiliser l’ingénierie inverse ou accéder d’une manière non autorisée ou automatisée à tout ordinateur, matériel, logiciel ou réseaux Nintendo utilisés pour fournir les Services en Ligne ou toute fonctionnalité d’un Appareil Nintendo;

 F. Tricher dans un jeu, à moins que de telles tricheries aient été délibérément permises par le Fournisseur de Contenu;

 G. Héberger, intercepter, émuler, utiliser l’ingénierie inverse ou rediriger les protocoles de communication utilisés par Nintendo dans le cadre d’un Appareil Nintendo ou des Services en Ligne, peu importe la méthode empruntée pour y parvenir; ou commettre un acte dans le but de contourner des mesures prises pour limiter l’accès à toute partie, tout contenu ou code d’un Appareil Nintendo ou des Services en Ligne (sauf si cela est expressément permis par la loi);

 H. Développer des applications de parties tierces entrant en interaction avec le Contenu Utilisateur et les Services en Ligne sans notre consentement écrit préalable;

 I. Entreprendre quelque activité commerciale que ce soit en utilisant un Appareil Nintendo ou les Services en Ligne; entreprendre quelque autre activité que ce soit qui nuit au fonctionne]]></main_text><main_text index="9"><![CDATA[ment, diminue la qualité ou interfère avec le fonctionnement d’un Appareil Nintendo, des Services en Ligne ou les services d’une partie tierce;

 J. Utiliser un robot Web ou tout autre outil ou interface automatique qui n’est pas fourni par nous pour accéder à des informations d’un Appareil Nintendo ou des Services en Ligne, ou en extraire des données;

 K. Télécharger, publier, envoyer par courriel, transmettre ou rendre disponible : (i) tout contenu ou donnée que vous n’avez pas le droit de rendre disponible en vertu de la loi; (ii) tout contenu ou donnée qui viole tout brevet, marque de commerce, secret commercial, droit d’auteur ou autre propriété intellectuelle ou tout autre droit de propriété de toute partie; (iii) toute publicité ou matériel promotionnel non sollicités ou non autorisés; (iv) du contenu ou des données dont vous avez déguisé l’origine; (v) des virus, des données altérées, ou autres fichiers dommageables, perturbants ou destructeurs; (vi) du contenu ou des données contenant des renseignements privés de quelque tiers que ce soit, y compris mais sans s’y limiter, des noms, adresses, adresses de courriel ou des données de cartes de crédit; ou (vii) du contenu ou des données obscènes, illégaux ou qui violent ce Contrat, ou qui dont la publication est interdite à l’intérieur de votre juridiction.

8. Réserve de droits et intérêts.

Les Services en Ligne vous sont fournis sur la base d’une licence limitée et ne vous sont pas vendus. À part votre licence limitée vous permettant d’utiliser les Services en Ligne comme stipulé expressément dans le présent Contrat, nous conservons tous les droits, titres et intérêts sur tous les Services en Ligne y compris, sans s’y limiter, tout droit de brevet, de droit d’auteur et de marque de commerce associés et tout autre droit de propriété ou de propriété intellectuelle de toute sorte dans tout pays.

9. Exclusion de garanties et limitation de responsabilité.

L’UTILISATION DES SERVICES EN LIGNE ET DES SERVICES DE TIERCES PARTIES EST À VOTRE SEUL RISQUE. AUCUN RE]]></main_text><main_text index="10"><![CDATA[NSEIGNEMENT ORAL OU ÉCRIT FOURNI PAR NINTENDO OU SES REPRÉSENTANTS NE CRÉE UNE GARANTIE. LES SERVICES EN LIGNE SONT FOURNIS « TELS QUELS » SANS AUCUNE GARANTIE. NINTENDO DÉCLINE TOUTE GARANTIE, EXPRESSE OU TACITE, EN CE QUI CONCERNE LES SERVICES EN LIGNE ET LES SERVICES DE TIERCES PARTIES, Y COMPRIS, SANS S’Y LIMITER, LES GARANTIES D’ABSENCE DE CONTREFAÇON, OU LES GARANTIES IMPLICITES DE COMMERCIALISATION ET D’ADAPTATION POUR UN USAGE PARTICULIER. DANS LES LIMITES AUTORISÉES PAR LA LOI, NINTENDO NE SERA PAS TENU RESPONSABLE ENVERS VOUS DE TOUT DOMMAGE SPÉCIAL OU INDIRECT DÉCOULANT OU LIÉ À VOTRE ACCÈS, UTILISATION, MAUVAISE UTILISATION OU INCAPACITÉ D’UTILISER LES SERVICES EN LIGNE OU TOUT SERVICE DE TIERCE PARTIE, MÊME SI NINTENDO A ÉTÉ INFORMÉ DE LA POSSIBILITÉ DE TELS DOMMAGES. EN TOUT CAS, LA RESPONSABILITÉ GLOBALE DE NINTENDO ENVERS VOUS EN LIEN AVEC TOUTE RÉCLAMATION DÉCOULANT OU ÉTANT ASSOCIÉE AUX SERVICES EN LIGNE ET AUX SERVICES DE TIERCES PARTIES SE LIMITE AU MONTANT QUE VOUS AVEZ RÉELLEMENT PAYÉ POUR LES SERVICES EN LIGNE FAISANT L’OBJET D’UNE TELLE RÉCLAMATION. SI UNE LOI RESTREINT NOTRE CAPACITÉ DE LIMITER LA RESPONSABILITÉ OU DE DÉCLINER DES GARANTIES, LES LIMITATIONS ÉNUMÉRÉES CI-DESSUS PEUVENT NE PAS S’APPLIQUER À VOUS. DANS CE CAS, NOUS LIMITONS NOTRE RESPONSABILITÉ ET DÉCLINONS LES GARANTIES DANS LES LIMITES MAXIMALES PERMISES PAR LA LOI.

10. Indemnité.

Si nous ou un de nos Affiliés, donneurs ou preneurs de licence, sous-traitants sommes soumis à de réelles réclamations ou menaces de réclamations, coûts, dommages, pertes, ou autres passifs (collectivement, « Pertes Assurées ») par suite de votre utilisation de tout Service en Ligne, Contenu Numérique, Appareil Nintendo, ou toute donnée, information ou autre item que vous rendez disponible par l’entremise des Services en Ligne ou d’un Appareil Nintendo, y compris le Contenu d’Utilisateur, alors vous convenez de nous indemniser (et nos Affiliés, donneurs ou preneurs de licence, sous-traitants et employés) pour de telles Pertes Assurées et de tou]]></main_text><main_text index="11"><![CDATA[t frais afférent, tel que les honoraires raisonnables d’avocats.

11. Rétroaction.

Séparément du Contenu d’Utilisateur, vous pouvez en général poser des questions, faire part de commentaires, de suggestions, d’idées, de plans, de notes, de dessin, de matériel original et créatif, et d’autres informations et matériels à propos de Nintendo et des Services en Ligne (la « Rétroaction »). La Rétroaction, qu’elle soit soumise par les Services en Ligneou d’une autre façon, n’est pas confidentielle et devient la propriété exclusive de Nintendo. Nous détiendrons des droits exclusifs, y compris tous les droits de propriété intellectuelle, sur cette rétroaction et nous serons autorisés à l’utiliser et à la diffuser à quelques fins que ce soit, commerciales ou non, sans reconnaissance ni compensation.

12. Règlement des différends; Arbitrage individuel obligatoire; Renonciation à une action de groupe.

 A. Notre service à la clientèle est disponible pour aborder toute inquiétude que vous pourriez avoir relativement à votre Compte Réseau ou aux Services en Ligne. Vous pouvez communiquer par téléphone avec le service à la clientèle au 1-800-255-3700, par courriel au useragreement@noa.nintendo.com, ou par courrier ordinaire à l’adresse suivante : Nintendo of America Inc., Attn : User Agreement, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052 É.-U. La plupart des cas sont rapidement résolus de cette manière à la satisfaction de nos clients. Tout cas qu’il nous est impossible de résoudre et tout litige ou réclamation découlant ou associé à ce Contrat, y compris sa formation, son caractère exécutoire, sa performance ou violation (chacun, une « Réclamation »), faisant exception des questions évoquées à la section 12 (C) ci-dessous sera définitivement réglé par arbitrage obligatoire administré par l’American Arbitration Association conformément aux dispositions de ses règles d’arbitrage commercial ainsi que les procédures supplémentaires pour les différends reliés aux consommateurs de l’American Arbitration Association (la « AAA »), excluant ]]></main_text><main_text index="12"><![CDATA[toute règle ou procédure gouvernant ou permettant les recours collectifs. L’arbitre, et non une cour ou une agence locale, d’état ou fédérale, aura le pouvoir exclusif de régler toutes les réclamations. L’arbitre aura le pouvoir d’accorder toute réparation qui serait disponible en cour conformément au droit ou en équité. La récompense attribuée par l’arbitre sera contraignante pour les parties et pourra faire office de verdict devant tout tribunal compétent. Les parties comprennent qu’en l’absence de cette disposition obligatoire, ils auraient le droit de poursuivre devant les tribunaux avec un procès devant jury. Elles comprennent également qu’en certaines circonstances, les coûts de l’arbitrage pourraient excéder les coûts du litige et le droit à une procédure de communication pourrait être davantage limité en arbitrage qu’en cour. Un tel arbitrage doit être effectué par les parties en leur capacité personnelle uniquement et non en tant qu’action de groupe ou autre action représentative, et les parties renoncent à leur droit à une action de groupe ou à rechercher un redressement sur une base collective. Si une cour ou un arbitre détermine que la renonciation à l’action de groupe mise de l’avant dans la phrase précédente est nulle et inapplicable pour une quelconque raison ou qu’un arbitrage peut s’effectuer sur base d’action de groupe, alors, la disposition d’arbitrage mise de l’avant en cette section 12 sera considérée comme nulle et non avenue dans son entier et les parties seront réputées ne pas avoir accepté d’arbitrer des Réclamations.

 B. Les règles régissant l’arbitrage peuvent être consultées au www.adr.org ou en téléphonant la AAA au +1.800.778.7879. Dans la mesure où le dépôt judiciaire initial pour l’arbitrage excède le dépôt judiciaire pour une action en justice, nous paierons la différence en frais. Si l’arbitre constate que l’arbitrage est non frivole, nous paierons le dépôt judiciaire et les honoraires de l’arbitre pour l’arbitrage en entier, à condition que votre réclamation soit inférieure au ]]></main_text><main_text index="13"><![CDATA[montant de 75 000 $. En certains cas, les règles d’arbitrage vous permettent également de recouvrer les honoraires d’avocats.

 C. La section 12(A) ne s’applique pas à une quelconque Réclamation (i) à l’intérieur de laquelle une partie tente de protéger ses droits de propriété intellectuelle (tel que son brevet, droit d’auteur, marque de commerce, secret commercial, ou droits moraux, mais n’incluant pas ses droits de confidentialité ou de publicité), ou (ii) qui peut être présentée au tribunal des petites créances.

 D. Droit de retrait d’une durée de 30 jours : Vous avez le droit de vous retirer des dispositions de cette Section 12 en faisant parvenir par écrit votre décision de vous retirer à l’adresse suivante : Nintendo of America Inc., Attn : CS Admin, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052 dans les 30 jours suivant la création de votre Compte Réseau. Votre avis doit inclure votre numéro de compte. Si vous envoyez cet avis, la Section 12 ne s’appliquera donc pas à aucune des parties. Si vous n’envoyez pas cet avis, vous acceptez d’être lié par cette Section 12.

13. Général.

 A. Violation; Résiliation; Survie. Ce contrat prendra fin automatiquement si vous vous ne vous conformez pas à ce Contrat. Dans le cas d’une telle résiliation, vous devez immédiatement cesser toute utilisation des Services en Ligne. Les Sections 3, 5, 6, 8, 9, 10, 12 et 13 de ce Contrat demeureront en vigueur à la suite d’une telle résiliation.

 B. Changements aux Services en Ligne; Livraison de Services en Ligne. Nous sommes en mesure de modifier, d’annuler, ou de suspendre la disponibilité des Services en Ligne en tout ou en partie en tout temps et sans préavis. Nous pouvons impliquer des Affiliés ou de tierces parties dans la livraison de Services en Ligne ou dans l’exécution de nos engagements dans le cadre de ce Contrat.

 C. Application; Non-renonciation; Non-cession. Si une quelconque partie de ce Contrat est déclarée invalide ou n’ayant pas force exécutoire, cette partie ne s’appliquera plus aux parties et sera remplacée par une]]></main_text><main_text index="14"><![CDATA[ disposition exécutoire qui reflète au mieux l’intention de départ des parties, mais toute autre partie de ce Contrat demeurera en vigueur, sauf disposition contraire du présent Contrat. En cas d’incapacité de notre part d’insister sur ou de faire exécuter strictement ce Contrat ne constituera pas une renonciation à un quelconque de nos droits. Vous ne pouvez céder vos droits ou intérêts à une autre personne en vertu de ce Contrat.

 D. Loi applicable. Les lois de l’état de Washington, É.-U., sans égard à ses dispositions concernant les conflits de lois, feront autorité sur ce Contrat et sur tout litige de quelque nature que ce soit pouvant survenir entre vous et Nintendo.

 E. Lieu. Si la Section 12 est déclarée invalide ou n’ayant pas force exécutoire, alors pour toute Réclamation, les parties se soumettent à la juridiction exclusive des tribunaux situés dans King County, Washington, É.-U.

 F. Pas de tiers bénéficiaire. Le présent Contrat s’applique dans l’intérêt unique des parties, qui seules peuvent faire valoir leur droits. Le présent Contrat n’a pas pour objet de conférer des droits ou des avantages à des tierces parties, quelles qu’elles soient, ni de créer des obligations auxdites parties.

 G. Modification des modalités. Nous pouvons modifier les modalités de ce Contrat en tout temps et sans avis. Une version actuelle de ce Contrat, y compris toute modification, est affichée à votre attention au support.nintendo.com. Dans le cas où vous n’accepteriez pas les changements apportés à ce Contrat, vous devez annuler votre Compte Réseau et cesser l’utilisation des Services en Ligne.

 H. Avis. Pour communiquer avec notre service à la clientèle concernant ce Contrat, vous pouvez (i) faire parvenir un courriel à useragreement@noa.nintendo.com; (ii) faire parvenir une lettre à Nintendo of America Inc., Attn : User Agreement, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052 É.-U.; ou (iii) téléphoner sans frais au 1-888-977-7627. Vos communications avec notre service à la clientèle ne constituera pas un avis légal là où req]]></main_text><main_text index="15"><![CDATA[uis par le Contrat ou par la loi.

Pour tout autre aspect juridique, vous devez nous contacter ou nous aviser par écrit à : Nintendo of America Inc., Attn : Conseil Général, 4600 150th Ave NE, Redmond, WA 98052.

Nous pourrions vous aviser relativement à ce Contrat par : (i) courriel à l’adresse associée à votre Compte Réseau; ou (ii) par des messages affichés dans Nintendo eShop, le Site Web Nintendo, ou autres lieux dont nous vous ferons part de temps en temps. Ces avis entreront en vigueur à la date de la livraison ou de la publication. Assurez-vous de maintenir à jour l’adresse courriel associée à votre Compte Réseau.

 I. Avis et Procédure d’allégation de violation des droits d’auteur. Nintendo respecte la propriété intellectuelle des autres et nous demandons aux utilisateurs des produits et services Nintendo à faire de même. Si vous estimez que vos droits de propriété intellectuelle ont été violés, veuillez consulter www.nintendo.com/ippolicy afin de lire notre politique intégrale et de soumettre une demande de retrait.

*** Fin d’Accord de Services En Ligne Nintendo***




Politique de confidentialité de Nintendo

Dernière mise à jour : 2 juillet 2015

Nintendo sait que la protection de vos renseignements personnels vous importe. Cette Politique de confidentialité décrit de quelle façon nous recueillons, utilisons, divulguons, stockons et protégeons vos renseignements. En utilisant un produit ou service Nintendo, vous acceptez les pratiques décrites dans cette Politique de confidentialité.

1. VOS RENSEIGNEMENTS

Les renseignements que vous nous fournissez. Nous recueillons les renseignements que vous nous fournissez lorsque vous utilisez nos produits et services ou chaque fois que vous entrez en contact avec nous.

Parmi les types de renseignements que vous nous fournissez, on compte :

 * les renseignements que vous êtes tenu de fournir lorsque vous vous inscrivez afin d’utiliser nos services, notamment votre nom, votre adresse, votre numéro de téléphone et votre adresse courriel;
 * les coordonnées d’ou]]></main_text><main_text index="16"><![CDATA[verture de session que vous utilisez pour vous connecter à nos services, comme votre nom d’utilisateur et votre mot de passe;
 * les renseignements démographiques vous concernant, notamment votre âge, votre sexe, vos passe-temps, vos intérêts et votre pays de résidence;
 * les coordonnées de paiement que vous envoyez, notamment votre numéro de carte de crédit, la date d’expiration et le code de sécurité de votre carte lorsqu’ils sont nécessaires pour effectuer une transaction que vous avez entreprise;
 * les messages, photos, vidéos, dessins, enregistrements audio et autres renseignements échangés par vous par le biais des fonctions interactives de nos produits et services;
 * la correspondance que vous nous envoyez directement; et
 * les renseignements que vous nous fournissez hors ligne (par exemple, par courrier postal, en personne, dans des formulaires d’inscription à un tirage, lors de transaction de service aux consommateurs comme des réparations, des commandes de pièces et des achats directs).

Les renseignements que nous recueillons automatiquement. Nous recueillons automatiquement certains renseignements lorsque vous utilisez nos produits et services.

Parmi les types de renseignements que nous pouvons recueillir automatiquement, on compte :

 * les renseignements au sujet de votre utilisation de nos produits, services et sites Web, notamment le type de votre navigateur, votre système d’exploitation, votre plate-forme, votre adresse IP, votre adresse MAC, votre langue et votre région;
 * les renseignements au sujet des sites Web que vous avez visités avant et après avoir visité les nôtres, les recherches que vous avez lancées et qui vous ont fait atterrir sur nos sites Web, les recherches que vous avez lancées sur nos sites Web, les pages et publicités que vous avez regardées de même que les liens sur lesquels vous avez cliqué en utilisant nos sites Web;
 * les renseignements au sujet de votre appareil Nintendo, notamment le numéro de série de l’appareil, son numéro d’identification , le point d’accès sa]]></main_text><main_text index="17"><![CDATA[ns fil et autres renseignements techniques à propos de votre appareil; et
 * les renseignements au sujet de vos séances de jeu, de votre statut en ligne, de votre utilisation de nos services en ligne, de vos amis et des codes de vos amis, de vos achats et des autres renseignements au sujet de vos interactions avec nos produits et services.

Les renseignements que nous recevons d’autres sources. Il arrive que nous recevions d’autres renseignements sur vous provenant d’autres sources, notamment de services et détaillants de tierce partie.

Parmi les exemples de renseignements que nous recevons d’autres sources, on compte :

 * les données de navigation, y compris les sites Web visités et les publicités vues ou sur lesquelles vous avez cliqué;
 * les renseignements au sujet de transactions de service aux consommateurs; et
 * les coordonnées d'achat.

Veuillez noter que nous pouvons ajouter des renseignements que nous recevons d’autres sources à ceux que nous possédons déjà sur vous. Nous pouvons aussi combiner vos renseignements à ceux d’autres utilisateurs, y compris les renseignements sur vos séances de jeu, les données démographiques, les critères de recherche, les parcours de navigation et les coordonnées d’achat, et utiliser ces renseignements combinés sous forme regroupée.

2. TÉMOINS, PIXELS INVISIBLES, FICHIERS HISTORIQUES ET PARTENAIRES DE TIERCE PARTIE

Afin de recueillir certains des renseignements décrits ci-dessus, il peut arriver d'utiliser des pixels invisibles, des témoins, des fichiers historiques et d’autres technologies similaires dans certains de nos produits et services, y compris dans nos courriels.

 * Pixels invisibles : Nous pouvons utiliser des pixels invisibles (aussi appelés pixels-espions ou GIF invisibles), qui sont de petites images graphiques placées sur une page ou un document Web, ou dans un courriel. Les pixels invisibles sont conçus pour recueillir certains renseignements sur l’utilisateur et assurer le suivi de certaines ses activités. Les renseignements recueillis par les pixels]]></main_text><main_text index="18"><![CDATA[ invisibles peuvent inclure votre adresse IP, adresse MAC, l’URL de la page sur laquelle vous vous trouviez, vos interactions avec notre site Web ou un courriel que nous vous envoyons. Nous pouvons utiliser les renseignements recueillis par le biais de pixels invisibles pour déterminer par exemple, comment améliorer certains produits et services en identifiant les pages Web, fonctions et produits les plus populaires; pour personnaliser nos produits et services; pour faire des recommandations de produits et services, et pour réaliser les transactions que vous avez demandées.
 * Témoins : Nous pouvons utiliser des témoins, qui sont des identifiants uniques parfois placés sur votre appareil dans le but d’enregistrer des données sur vos visites sur un site Web afin que ce dernier puisse reconnaître votre appareil et personnaliser votre visite. Les renseignements recueillis par les témoins peuvent être liés à l’historique de vos transactions, vos séances de jeu en ligne ou à toute autre information. Nous pouvons utiliser les renseignements recueillis par le biais de témoins pour déterminer par exemple, comment améliorer certains produits et services en identifiant les pages Web, fonctions et produits les plus populaires; pour personnaliser nos produits et services; pour faire des recommandations de produits et services, et pour réaliser les transactions que vous avez demandées. Vous pouvez régler certains navigateurs de manière à rejeter les témoins ou à vous aviser lorsqu'on vous envoie un témoin. Toutefois, la non-utilisation des témoins pourrait vous empêcher d'utiliser certaines fonctions et fonctionnalités de nos produits et services.
 * Fichiers historiques : Nous conservons des fichiers historiques qui enregistrent toute activité liée à l’utilisation de nos produits et services, comme la fréquence de consultation d’une page Web particulière, le type et la qualité de la connexion Internet d’un utilisateur, le type de matériel et/ou de logiciel utilisé pour accéder à un service particulier, les fonctions utilisée]]></main_text><main_text index="19"><![CDATA[s d’un service et leur fréquence d’utilisation. Les entrées dans ces fichiers historiques peuvent inclure par exemple, vos adresses IP, adresses MAC, renseignements sur les témoins, l’identifiant de votre appareil, vos données de transaction, les paramètres de votre appareil et votre activité de téléchargement. Nous utilisons ces fichiers historiques par exemple, pour assurer le suivi du trafic sur notre site Web, pour faciliter l’utilisation de certains services et pour assurer le dépannage de problèmes techniques.
 * Partenaires de tierce partie : Il nous arrive également de permettre à nos partenaires de tierce partie d’établir des témoins, des pixels invisibles et des technologies similaires sur nos sites Web ou dans les courriels qui vous sont envoyés en notre nom afin de nous aider à exécuter certaines fonctions internes nécessaires au bon déroulement de nos activités. Ces tierces parties peuvent aussi utiliser ces témoins, pixels invisibles et autres technologies similaires pour recueillir des renseignements au sujet de votre visite sur nos sites Web et ailleurs sur Internet, renseignements dont ils peuvent se servir pendant ou après vos visites sur nos sites Web pour vous fournir des publicités au sujet de biens et de services qui pourraient vous intéresser. Certaines de ces tierces parties peuvent vous offrir une option d’exclusion de ce type de ciblage publicitaire par des mécanismes de choix d'industrie. Pour en savoir sur les tierces parties qui participent à ces offres de choix et pour exercer ceux qui peuvent être mis à votre disposition, allez sur www.networkadvertising.org et www.aboutads.info.

3. UTILISATION DES RENSEIGNEMENTS

Vos renseignements peuvent être utilisés par nous, nos sociétés affiliées ou nos partenaires de tierce partie ou nous dans le but de : (i) répondre à vos demandes de produits, de services et d’information, notamment pour vous envoyer des messages commerciaux et non commerciaux et pour traiter les commandes que vous avez passées; (ii) vous contacter au sujet de nos produit]]></main_text><main_text index="20"><![CDATA[s et services, y compris à des fins promotionnelles et de marketing; (iii) faciliter votre utilisation de nos produits, services et sites Web; (iv) activer votre participation à des jeux en ligne, concours, tirages, sondages, forums publics et autres fonctions offertes par nos produits, services et sites Web; (v) faire des recommandations et personnaliser le contenu, les fonctions et la publicité accessibles par le biais de nos produits, services et sites Web; (vi) établir des bons de réparation et répondre aux demandes de service de la part des consommateurs; (vii) fournir des services dorsaux, y compris des mises à jour de système, des messages système; (viii) fournir des jeux, applications essais gratuits et autre contenu; (ix) analyser et faciliter l’utilisation de nos produits, services et sites Web; (x) faciliter les études démographiques; (xi) comprendre, améliorer et développer nos produits et services; (xii) prévenir les éventuelles activités illicites ou offensantes; (xiii) rendre exécutoires nos droits ou ceux de nos utilisateurs; (xiv) vérifier votre identité et prévenir les transactions frauduleuses; et (xv) à toutes autres fins qui vous sont divulguées au moment où nous recueillons vos renseignements ou concernant votre consentement.

4. DIVULGATION DES RENSEIGNEMENTS

De temps à autre, nous mettons certains des renseignements que nous recueillons à la disposition de nos sociétés affiliées, de nos partenaires de tierce partie, des autres utilisateurs Nintendo, au grand public et à d’autres fins légales et commerciales. Par exemple :

 * Sociétés affiliées de Nintendo. Nous pouvons échanger des renseignements avec d’autres sociétés affiliées de Nintendo qui les utilisent conformément à cette Politique de confidentialité.
 * Tierces parties. Nous pouvons échanger des renseignements avec nos partenaires de tierce partie afin de nous aider à exécuter diverses fonctions nécessaires à l’exploitation de notre entreprise ou pour répondre à vos demandes (par exemple, pour effectuer des téléchargements ou des]]></main_text><main_text index="21"><![CDATA[ achats, pour développer et mettre à exécution des campagnes de marketing). Nous pouvons aussi échanger de tels renseignements, par exemple, afin de conclure vos transactions, de vous fournir de la documentation publicitaire ou promotionnelle et vous aider à créer des comptes d’utilisateur avec de telles tierces parties.
 * Autres utilisateurs et amis. Nous pouvons échanger des renseignements, y compris, par exemple, votre surnom Mii, information de profil Mii, statut en ligne, message d’accueil Mii et autres renseignements sur votre jeu avec d’autres utilisateurs Nintendo lorsque vous utilisez les fonctions de nos produits et services.
 * Grand public. Lorsque vous utilisez certains de nos services en ligne, par exemple lorsque vous jouez à des jeux en ligne ou publiez sur Miiverse, votre nom d'utilisateur, surnom, profil d'utilisateur ainsi que certains renseignements relatifs aux séances de jeu peuvent être affichés sur Internet et vus par le grand public.
 * Communications locales. Certains appareils Nintendo sont dotés de fonctions de communication locales que vous pouvez activer. Par l’utilisation de ces fonctions, certains de vos renseignements sont automatiquement recueillis par nous et échangés avec nous et d’autres utilisateurs Nintendo. Ces fonctions nous permettent, ainsi qu’aux autres utilisateurs Nintendo, de vous contacter et d’interagir automatiquement avec vous. Lorsque vous activez ces fonctions, vous pouvez recevoir des renseignements et des communications d’autres utilisateurs Nintendo, de même que du matériel publicitaire et promotionnel de la part de Nintendo et de ses partenaires de tierce partie. Vous pouvez désactiver ces fonctions de communication locale à n’importe quel moment en réglant les paramètres de votre appareil Nintendo.
 * Fins légales et commerciales. Nous pouvons divulguer vos renseignements afin de nous conformer aux processus légaux, de répondre aux réclamations ou demandes, ou dans le but de protéger les droits, la propriété ou la sécurité personnelle de Nintendo, de nos ]]></main_text><main_text index="22"><![CDATA[utilisateurs ou du public. Vos renseignements peuvent aussi être divulgués dans le cadre de toute vente ou tout transfert des biens de la société, lorsque la loi le permet.

Vous êtes responsable des renseignements que vous échangez avec d’autres par l’utilisation de nos produits, services et sites Web. Vous devez savoir que les autres utilisateurs peuvent stocker, modifier ou échanger avec des tiers les renseignements que vous leur fournissez.

5. LIAISON DE COMPTES

Nous pouvons vous offrir un compte pour un ou plusieurs de nos programmes de fidélisation, y compris le Club Nintendo, pour que vous ayez l’occasion de recevoir un contenu personnalisé et de participer à une variété d’activités, de promotions et de programmes. Dans les limites de certains paramètres, il vous est possible de lier votre appareil Nintendo ou compte de réseau à votre compte de fidélisation. Dans de telles circonstances, nous utiliserons vos renseignements, par exemple, pour enregistrer vos achats dans votre compte de fidélisation afin que vous ayez la possibilité de recevoir des récompenses et des promotions. Vous avez l’option d’annuler la mise en liaison de ces comptes dans la section des paramètres de Nintendo eShop.

6. TIERCES PARTIES

Vos renseignements peuvent être divulgués à des tierces parties lorsque vous utilisez nos produits et services pour jouer à des jeux de tierce partie, utiliser des applications ou plugiciels de tierce partie, regarder des publicités ou visiter des sites Web de tierce partie. Nous ne sommes pas responsables des pratiques de confidentialité de ces tierces parties et nous vous recommandons à ce titre de lire leurs politiques de confidentialité avant de leur soumettre tout renseignement.

7. MISE EN GARDE DESTINÉE AUX PARENTS OU TUTEURS LÉGAUX : PROTECTION DE LA VIE PRIVÉE DES ENFANTS

Conformément à la loi applicable, nous obtenons le consentement des parents pour la collecte de renseignements sur leurs enfants. Vous trouverez l’information portant sur la façon dont nous recueillons, utilisons et divulg]]></main_text><main_text index="23"><![CDATA[uons les renseignements personnels de nos utilisateurs, y compris les enfants âgés de moins de 13 ans, dans les sections ci-dessus intitulées VOS RENSEIGNEMENTS, UTILISATION DES RENSEIGNEMENTS et DIVULGATION DES RENSEIGNEMENTS.

Vous pouvez examiner ou demander de supprimer les renseignements personnels que nous avons recueillis sur vos enfants. Vous pouvez également refuser votre consentement à ce que nous recueillions ou utilisions à l’avenir des renseignements personnels sur vos enfants en contactant un administrateur de la confidentialité Nintendo par courriel à l’adresse privacypolicy@noa.nintendo.com, par téléphone au 1 888 977-7627, ou par courrier postal en écrivant à Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: Nintendo Privacy Administrator, 4600 150th Avenue NE, Redmond, WA 98052, U.S.A. Avant de répondre à votre demande d’examiner les renseignements personnels recueillis sur votre enfant, nous pouvons exiger que vous vous conformiez à des directives raisonnables visant à nous aider à vérifier votre identité en tant que parent ou tuteur légal de l’enfant en question. Nous pouvons refuser toute demande qui ne se conforme pas à ces directives. Si vous choisissez de faire supprimer les renseignements personnels sur votre enfant ou si vous refusez votre consentement à la collecte ou l’utilisation ultérieure de tels renseignements, il est possible que certaines fonctions de nos produits et services soient limitées ou inaccessibles.

Veuillez noter que les éditeurs de jeux, fournisseurs d’applications et de contenu de tierce partie peuvent recueillir, utiliser et divulguer les renseignements personnels de votre enfant par le biais de nos produits et services lorsque votre enfant utilise des services ou un contenu de tierce partie. Nintendo n'est pas responsable des pratiques de confidentialité de ces tierces parties et nous vous recommandons à ce titre de lire leurs politiques de confidentialité avant que votre enfant fournisse ou échange tout renseignement personnel par le biais de services ou de contenu de tierce parti]]></main_text><main_text index="24"><![CDATA[e.

Il est fortement conseillé de superviser en tout temps l’utilisation de nos produits et services par votre enfant. Vous pouvez restreindre l’utilisation par vos enfants de certaines fonctions de nos produits et services en configurant les paramètres de contrôle parental sur votre appareil Nintendo. Pour une description détaillée de ces fonctions de contrôle parental, veuillez consulter le manuel de l’utilisateur de votre appareil Nintendo.

8. SÉCURITÉ

Nintendo prend des précautions raisonnables et a mis en place des mesures de protection raisonnables visant à protéger vos renseignements contre les pertes, le vol, l’utilisation malicieuse, l’accès non autorisé, la divulgation, la modification et la destruction de ceux-ci. Vous devez toutefois comprendre qu’aucun système de stockage ou de transmission de données sur Internet ou sur tout autre réseau public ne peut garantir qu’il est sécurisé à 100 %.

Veuillez noter que les renseignements recueillis par des tierces parties ne bénéficient pas nécessairement des mêmes mesures de sécurité que ceux que vous nous envoyez ou que nous recueillons; nous ne sommes donc pas responsables de la protection de tels renseignements.

Si vous installez sur votre appareil Nintendo ou sur son logiciel des applications non autorisées ou un contenu non autorisé, ou si vous y apportez des modifications non autorisées, vos renseignements pourraient être compromis. Nintendo n’est pas responsable de la collecte, de l’utilisation ou de la divulgation des renseignements provenant de tout appareil Nintendo sur lequel des modifications non autorisées ont été apportées ou qui contient un logiciel ou un contenu non autorisé.

9. OPTION D’EXCLUSION

Vous pouvez utiliser un appareil Nintendo sans nous fournir vos renseignements; toutefois, il est possible que certaines fonctions et applications ne vous soient pas accessibles. Vous avez l’option d’être exclus de la collecte de certains renseignements en n’utilisant pas nos services. Vous pouvez également vous exclure de la collecte de certain]]></main_text><main_text index="25"><![CDATA[s types de renseignements en réglant les paramètres de votre appareil Nintendo, ses contrôles parentaux ou autres mécanismes d’exclusion qui sont mis à votre disposition. Certains renseignements techniques regroupés à propos de votre appareil Nintendo peuvent toujours continuer d’être recueillis automatiquement lorsque vous, ou un autre utilisateur de votre appareil, vous connectez à Internet. Vous pouvez choisir de ne pas recevoir de courriels de nature commerciale de la part de Nintendo en suivant les instructions contenues dans de tels courriels.

10. SUPPRESSION DES RENSEIGNEMENTS STOCKÉS SUR VOTRE APPAREIL NINTENDO

Certains renseignements à votre sujet peuvent être stockés sur votre appareil Nintendo. Pour votre protection, veillez à supprimer toute information stockée sur votre appareil Nintendo, y compris toute information stockée sur les accessoires de l’appareil avant de vendre ce dernier, de le transférer ou d’en disposer. Pour des instructions sur la façon de supprimer l’information stockée sur votre appareil Nintendo, veuillez consulter le manuel de l’utilisateur ou allez à support.nintendo.com.

Si vous transférez des données d’un appareil Nintendo à un autre à l’aide de nos outils ou fonctions de transfert du système, t.out renseignement à votre sujet stocké sur cet appareil sera transféré dans le cadre du processus

11. UTILISATEURS INTERNATIONAUX

Tout renseignement que vous fournissez ou qui est recueilli par le biais de l’utilisation de nos produits, services ou sites Web peut être stocké, traité et transféré sur le territoire des États-Unis, vers les États-Unis ou tout autre pays dans lequel nos sociétés affiliées, nos partenaires de tierce partie ou nous avons des installations. En conséquence, il est possible que des autorités gouvernementales ou autres autorités étrangères aient accès à vos renseignements, conformément aux lois locales en vigueur. Par l’utilisation du site Web basé aux États-Unis, ou en désignant les États-Unis en tant que région pour votre appareil Nintendo, vous consentez]]></main_text><main_text index="26"><![CDATA[ de fait à la collecte, au stockage, au traitement et au transfert de vos renseignements sur le territoire des États-Unis, vers les États-Unis ou tout autre pays ou territoire, conformément aux lois des États-Unis. Nous respectons le cadre théorique de la règle refuge (Safe Harbor Framework) des É.-U.-U.E. ainsi que celui de la règle refuge (Safe Harbor Framework É.-U.-Suisse, tel que défini par le Département du commerce américain concernant la collecte, l’utilisation et la rétention des données provenant de l’Espace économique européen et de la Suisse. Pour de plus amples renseignements concernant la règle refuge et pour consulter nos documents de certification, visitez le site Web du Safe Harbor du Département du commerce américain.

12. MODIFICATIONS DE CETTE POLITIQUE DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ

Nous pouvons mettre à jour de temps à autre cette Politique de confidentialité. Le cas échéant, nous modifierons la date de « dernière mise à jour » indiquée ci-haut. Les mises à jour seront publiées sur support.nintendo.com. Nous vous recommandons de lire cette Politique de confidentialité chaque fois que vous utilisez nos produits, services ou sites Web afin de vous tenir informé au sujet de nos pratiques de confidentialité.

13. CERTIFICATION DE L’ESRB

Cette Politique de confidentialité et le sceau de certification qui figure sur notre site Web confirment notre statut de titulaire de licence en règle et de membre participant au programme certifié de confidentialité en ligne de l’Entertainment Software Rating Board. Afin de protéger vos renseignements personnels, nous avons volontairement pris cette initiative de confidentialité. En tant que titulaire d’une licence de ce programme de certification de la confidentialité, nos sites Web font fréquemment l’objet de vérifications et d’autres mécanismes exécutoires et de reddition de comptes administrés de manière indépendante par l’ESRB. Nos sites arborant le sceau de certification ESRB ont tous été examinés et certifiés par l’ESRB comme répondant aux normes établies de pratiq]]></main_text><main_text index="27"><![CDATA[ues de collecte et d’utilisation des renseignements.

14. CONTACTEZ-NOUS POUR TOUTE QUESTION, PRÉOCCUPATION OU TOUT COMMENTAIRE AU SUJET DE LA PROTECTION DE VOS RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS

Si vous avez des questions, des plaintes à formuler ou des commentaires concernant cet avis de protection des renseignements personnels ou l’une de nos pratiques de confidentialité, veuillez contacter un administrateur de la confidentialité Nintendo par courriel à privacypolicy@noa.nintendo.com, par téléphone au 1 888 977-7627, ou par courrier postal en écrivant à Nintendo of America Inc., Attn: Privacy Administrator, 4600 150th Avenue NE, Redmond, WA 98052, U.S.A.

Vous pouvez également communiquer avec l’ESRB Privacy Certified par courriel à privacy@esrb.org, ou par la poste à : ESRB Privacy Certified, Attn : Privacy Certified Program, 420 Lexington Avenue, Suite 2024, New York, NY 10017.

***Fin de la Politique de Confidentialité de Nintendo***
]]></main_text></texts><type>NINTENDO-NETWORK-EULA</type><version>0300</version></agreement></agreements>